<rules>
	<rule>
		<id>1</id>
		<field_name>Reporting Member state</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingMemberState&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Country code standard ISO-3166-1 of the Member State to which the AIFM reports the AIFMD reporting.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>FIL-009</error_reference>
		<control>Validate that the reporting member state attribute fits to the file name sender 2 characters of the file</control>
		<error_message>The authority key file attribute is not consistent with the sending</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>2</id>
		<field_name>Reporting Member state</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingMemberState&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Country code standard ISO-3166-1 of the Member State to which the AIFM reports the AIFMD reporting.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>FIL-015</error_reference>
		<control>Check that the reporting member state attribute of the report is listed in the reference table of countries and referenced as EEA country</control>
		<error_message>The authority key file attribute is invalid and should an EU or EEA country</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>4</id>
		<field_name>Filing type</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;FilingType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The filling types admitted are:
- AMND for "amendment to one reporting previously submitted "
- INIT for "initial reporting for the reporting period"</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-001</error_reference>
		<control>In the file received by ESMA, if for one record, the filing type is equal to “INIT” and that this record has been previously integrated in the ESMA database, the whole record will not be integrated.</control>
		<error_message>The AIF record with "INIT" filing type has been already provided and will not be recorded twice.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>6</id>
		<field_name>Reporting period start date</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingPeriodStartDate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The start date of the reporting period should begin on  the first calendar of January, April, July or October. yyyy-mm-dd (ISO 8601 Date Format)</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-002</error_reference>
		<control>For quarterly reporting (Q1, Q2, Q3, Q4) Validate that the reporting start date is the beginning of a quarter. Allowed values are YYYY-10-01, YYYY-07-01, YYYY-04-01, YYYY-01-01 For half-yearly reporting (H1, H2) Validate that the reporting start date is the beginning of a half-yearly period (H1, H2) Allowed values are YYYY-07-01, YYYY-01-01 For yearly reporting (Y1) Validate that the reporting start date is the beginning of the calendar year (Y1) Allowed value is YYYY-01-01</control>
		<error_message>The reporting period start date is not allowed.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>7</id>
		<field_name>Reporting period end date</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingPeriodEndDate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The end date of the reporting period may be the last calendar day of March, June, September, December or the last day the AIFM exists. yyyy-mm-dd (ISO 8601 Date Format)</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-003</error_reference>
		<control>Validate that the reporting end date is less or equal to the end of the last reporting period For quarterly reporting (Q1, Q2, Q3, Q4) Validate that the reporting end date is less or equal to YYYY-03-31 for Q1, YYYY-06-30 for Q2, YYYY-09-30 for Q3, YYYY-12-31 for Q4. For half-yearly reporting (H1, H2) Validate that the reporting end date is less or equal to YYYY-06-30 for H1,  YYYY-12-31 for H2. For yearly reporting (Y1) Validate that the reporting end date is less or equal to YYYY-12-31 for Y1.  When transition filling flag is false,  For quarterly reporting (Q1, Q2, Q3, Q4) Validate that the reporting end date is the end of a quarter. Allowed values are YYYY-03-31 for Q1, YYYY-06-30 for Q2, YYYY-09-30 for Q3, YYYY-12-31  for Q4 For half-yearly reporting (H1, H2) Validate that the reporting end date is the end of a 6-month period (H1, H2) Allowed values are YYYY-06-30 for H1, YYYY-12-31 for H2 For yearly reporting (Y1) Validate that the reporting end date is the end of the calendar year (Y1) Allowed value is YYYY-12-31 for Y1  Validate that the reporting end date is greater than the reporting start date.</control>
		<error_message>The reporting period end date is not allowed</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>12</id>
		<field_name>Change in AIFM reporting obligation Quarter</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFMReportingObligationChangeQuarter&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>
Code indicating the quarter during which the frequency and/or contents reporting obligation on the AIFM changes. The codes for the reporting obligation change quarter are:    - Q1: for 1st quarter of the calendar year    - Q2: for 2nd quarter of the calendar year    - Q3: for 3rd quarter of the calendar year    - Q4: for 4th quarter of the calendar year The field is mandatoty for
&lt;AIFMReportingObligationChangeFrequencyCode&gt;
or
&lt;AIFMReportingObligationChangeContentsCode&gt; filled in and forbidden otherwise.

</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-004</error_reference>
		<control>
The field is mandatory for
&lt;AIFReportingObligationChangeFrequencyCode&gt;
or
&lt;AIFReportingObligationChangeContentsCode&gt; filled in

</control>
		<error_message>The quarter for the AIMF reporting obligation change should be reported</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>17</id>
		<field_name>AIFM jurisdiction</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFMJurisdiction&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Jurisdiction in which the AIFM is established (Country code standard ISO-3166-1)</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-005</error_reference>
		<control>The country code exists in the reference table of countries</control>
		<error_message>The jurisdiction of the AIF is not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>18</id>
		<field_name>AIFM National Code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFMNationalCode&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Unique reference identifying each AIFM allocated by the national competent authority of the reporting Member State of the AIFM to which the AIFM reports under AIFMD</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-006</error_reference>
		<control>The AIFM national code exists in the ESMA register for the reporting Member State</control>
		<error_message>The AIFM national code does not exist in the ESMA Register.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>22</id>
		<field_name>AIFM LEI Code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFMIdentifierLEI&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Legal Entity Identifer (LEI) (ISO 17442 standard) of the Entity  or if not available the Interim Entity Identifier (IEI): •Characters 1-4: A four character prefix allocated uniquely to each LOU. •Characters 5-6: Two reserved characters set to zero. •Characters 7-18: Entity - specific part of the code generated and assigned by LOUs according to transparent, sound and robust allocation policies. •Characters 19-20: Two check digits </technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-007</error_reference>
		<control>Verify the correctness of the LEI code format rules following the calculation methodology of the 2-last check digits under validation rules using ISO 7064, Data Processing, Check Character Systems.</control>
		<error_message>Verify the correctness of the LEI code format rules following the calculation methodology of the 2-last check digits</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>24</id>
		<field_name>Old AIFM national identifier - Reporting Member State</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingMemberState&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Country code standard ISO-3166-1 of the reporting Member State which have allocated the former national identification code to provide when the national identification code changes (for the first reporting following the change of the national code and any subsequent reporting).</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-008</error_reference>
		<control>The country code exists in the reference table of countries</control>
		<error_message>The country code exists in the reference table of countries</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>25</id>
		<field_name>Old AIFM national identifier - National code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFMNationalCode&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Former national identification code to provide when the national identification code of the AIFM changes (for the first reporting following the change of the national code and any subsequent reporting). The field is mandatory when the  old AIFM national identifier - Reporting Member State is filled in.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-009</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory when the  old AIFM national identifier - Reporting Member State is filled in.</control>
		<error_message>The field is mandatory when the  old AIFM national identifier - Reporting Member State is filled in.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>28</id>
		<field_name>MIC code of the principal market in which the AIFM trades</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;MarketCode&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The “MIC” code (ISO 10383) for trading venues where AIFMs trade. The field is mandatory when the market code type is equal to "MIC" and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-010</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory when the market code type is equal to "MIC" and forbidden otherwise. The MIC code exists in the reference table of markets. ESMA system will not use the validity start date and validity end date of the MIC code to identify the validity of the MIC code.</control>
		<error_message>The MIC code is not correct</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>29</id>
		<field_name>Aggregated value of the principal market in which the AIFM trades</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AggregatedValueAmount&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Aggregated value of the instruments aggregated at the level of the five most important markets in which it trades on behalf of the AIF it manages. Aggregated value expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places. The field is mandatory for market code type different from  “NOT”. The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-011</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for market code type different from  “NOT”.</control>
		<error_message>The field is mandatory for market code type different from  “NOT”.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>30</id>
		<field_name>Aggregated value of the principal market in which the AIFM trades</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AggregatedValueAmount&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Aggregated value of the instruments aggregated at the level of the five most important markets in which it trades on behalf of the AIF it manages. Aggregated value expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places. The field is mandatory for market code type different from  “NOT”. The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-012</error_reference>
		<control>The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on.</control>
		<error_message>The reported value is not consistent with the rank.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>32</id>
		<field_name>Aggregated value of the principal instrument</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AggregatedValueAmount&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Value of the instruments calculated as set out in Article 2 of the Regulation 231/2013 aggregated at the level of the sub-asset type expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places. The value of the instruments should be calculated as of the last business day of the reporting period. The field is mandatory for sub-asset type code different from “NTA_NTA_NOTA” and optional otherwise. The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on. Each rank should be reported once.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-013</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for sub-asset type code different from “NTA_NTA_NOTA” and optional otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The aggregated value is not consistent with the sub-asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id></id>
		<field_name>Aggregated value of the principal instrument</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AggregatedValueAmount&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Value of the instruments calculated as set out in Article 2 of the Regulation 231/2013 aggregated at the level of the sub-asset type expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places. The value of the instruments should be calculated as of the last business day of the reporting period. The field is mandatory for sub-asset type code different from “NTA_NTA_NOTA” and optional otherwise. The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on. Each rank should be reported once.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-014</error_reference>
		<control>The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on.</control>
		<error_message>The reported value is not consistent with the rank.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>35</id>
		<field_name>Total AuM amount in base currency</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AUMAmountInBaseCurrency&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Value in base currency of Assets under management (AuM) for all AIFs managed, (when all AIFs of the AIFM are denominated in one single same base currency that is not the Euro) using the method set out in Articles 2 and 10 of the Regulation 231/2013. The total AuM amount expressed in base currency is filled in without decimal places and when available should be equal to the total AuM amount in Euro * Base currency / EUR FX rate.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-016</error_reference>
		<control>The total AuM amount expressed in base currency should be equal to the total AuM amount in Euro * Base currency / EUR FX rate.</control>
		<error_message>The total AuM amount in base currency is not consistent with the  total AuM amount in Euro.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>35</id>
		<field_name>AIFM Base currency</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;BaseCurrency&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Base currency code (3-character currency code according to the ISO 4217 ) for all AIFs managed by the AIFM.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-017</error_reference>
		<control>The currency code exists in the reference table of countries</control>
		<error_message></error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>38</id>
		<field_name>Base currency / EUR FX reference rate description for no ECB rates</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;FXEUROtherReferenceRateDescription&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Name of the source of the euro reference rates used according to the FX EUR conversion reference rate type reported - Free text for “OTH” type when the corresponding euro reference rate is not published by the ECB - Empty for “ECB” type when the corresponding euro reference rate is published by the ECB The field is mandatory for Base currency / EUR FX reference rate type equal to "OTH" and forbidden otherwise</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-020</error_reference>
		<control> The field is mandatory for Base currency / EUR FX reference rate type equal to "OTH" and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The reference rate description is not consistent with the reference rate type.</error_message>
	</rule>

</rules>