<rules>
	<rule>
		<id>1</id>
		<field_name>Reporting Member state</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingMemberState&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Country code standard ISO-3166-1 of the Member State to which the AIFM reports the AIFMD reporting.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>FIL-009</error_reference>
		<control>Validate that the reporting member state attribute fits to the file name sender 2 characters of the file</control>
		<error_message>The authority key file attribute is not consistent with the sending</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>2</id>
		<field_name>Reporting Member state</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingMemberState&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Country code standard ISO-3166-1 of the Member State to which the AIFM reports the AIFMD reporting.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>FIL-015</error_reference>
		<control>Check that the reporting member state attribute of the report is listed in the reference table of countries and referenced as EEA country</control>
		<error_message>The authority key file attribute is invalid and should an EU or EEA country</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>4</id>
		<field_name>Filing type</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;FilingType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The filling types admitted are:
- AMND for "amendment to one reporting previously submitted "
- INIT for "initial reporting for the reporting period"</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-001</error_reference>
		<control>In the file received by ESMA, if for one record, the filing type is equal to “INIT” and that this record has been previously integrated in the ESMA database, the whole record will not be integrated.</control>
		<error_message>The AIF record with "INIT" filing type has been already provided and will not be recorded twice.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>6</id>
		<field_name>Reporting period start date</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingPeriodStartDate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The start date of the reporting period should begin on  the first calendar of January, April, July or October. yyyy-mm-dd (ISO 8601 Date Format)</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-002</error_reference>
		<control>For quarterly reporting (Q1, Q2, Q3, Q4) Validate that the reporting start date is the beginning of a quarter. Allowed values are YYYY-10-01, YYYY-07-01, YYYY-04-01, YYYY-01-01 For half-yearly reporting (H1, H2) Validate that the reporting start date is the beginning of a half-yearly period (H1, H2) Allowed values are YYYY-07-01, YYYY-01-01 For yearly reporting (Y1) Validate that the reporting start date is the beginning of the calendar year (Y1) Allowed value is YYYY-01-01</control>
		<error_message>The reporting period start date is not allowed.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>7</id>
		<field_name>Reporting period end date</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingPeriodEndDate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The end date of the reporting period may be the last calendar day of March, June, September, December or the last day the AIFM exists. yyyy-mm-dd (ISO 8601 Date Format)</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-003</error_reference>
		<control>Validate that the reporting end date is less or equal to the end of the last reporting period For quarterly reporting (Q1, Q2, Q3, Q4) Validate that the reporting end date is less or equal to YYYY-03-31 for Q1, YYYY-06-30 for Q2, YYYY-09-30 for Q3, YYYY-12-31 for Q4. For half-yearly reporting (H1, H2) Validate that the reporting end date is less or equal to YYYY-06-30 for H1,  YYYY-12-31 for H2. For yearly reporting (Y1) Validate that the reporting end date is less or equal to YYYY-12-31 for Y1.  When transition filling flag is false,  For quarterly reporting (Q1, Q2, Q3, Q4) Validate that the reporting end date is the end of a quarter. Allowed values are YYYY-03-31 for Q1, YYYY-06-30 for Q2, YYYY-09-30 for Q3, YYYY-12-31  for Q4 For half-yearly reporting (H1, H2) Validate that the reporting end date is the end of a 6-month period (H1, H2) Allowed values are YYYY-06-30 for H1, YYYY-12-31 for H2 For yearly reporting (Y1) Validate that the reporting end date is the end of the calendar year (Y1) Allowed value is YYYY-12-31 for Y1  Validate that the reporting end date is greater than the reporting start date.</control>
		<error_message>The reporting period end date is not allowed</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>12</id>
		<field_name>Change in AIFM reporting obligation Quarter</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFMReportingObligationChangeQuarter&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>
Code indicating the quarter during which the frequency and/or contents reporting obligation on the AIFM changes. The codes for the reporting obligation change quarter are:    - Q1: for 1st quarter of the calendar year    - Q2: for 2nd quarter of the calendar year    - Q3: for 3rd quarter of the calendar year    - Q4: for 4th quarter of the calendar year The field is mandatoty for
&lt;AIFMReportingObligationChangeFrequencyCode&gt;
or
&lt;AIFMReportingObligationChangeContentsCode&gt; filled in and forbidden otherwise.

</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-004</error_reference>
		<control>
The field is mandatory for
&lt;AIFReportingObligationChangeFrequencyCode&gt;
or
&lt;AIFReportingObligationChangeContentsCode&gt; filled in

</control>
		<error_message>The quarter for the AIMF reporting obligation change should be reported</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>17</id>
		<field_name>AIFM jurisdiction</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFMJurisdiction&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Jurisdiction in which the AIFM is established (Country code standard ISO-3166-1)</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-005</error_reference>
		<control>The country code exists in the reference table of countries</control>
		<error_message>The jurisdiction of the AIF is not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>18</id>
		<field_name>AIFM National Code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFMNationalCode&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Unique reference identifying each AIFM allocated by the national competent authority of the reporting Member State of the AIFM to which the AIFM reports under AIFMD</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-006</error_reference>
		<control>The AIFM national code exists in the ESMA register for the reporting Member State</control>
		<error_message>The AIFM national code does not exist in the ESMA Register.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>22</id>
		<field_name>AIFM LEI Code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFMIdentifierLEI&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Legal Entity Identifer (LEI) (ISO 17442 standard) of the Entity  or if not available the Interim Entity Identifier (IEI): •Characters 1-4: A four character prefix allocated uniquely to each LOU. •Characters 5-6: Two reserved characters set to zero. •Characters 7-18: Entity - specific part of the code generated and assigned by LOUs according to transparent, sound and robust allocation policies. •Characters 19-20: Two check digits </technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-007</error_reference>
		<control>Verify the correctness of the LEI code format rules following the calculation methodology of the 2-last check digits under validation rules using ISO 7064, Data Processing, Check Character Systems.</control>
		<error_message>Verify the correctness of the LEI code format rules following the calculation methodology of the 2-last check digits</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>24</id>
		<field_name>Old AIFM national identifier - Reporting Member State</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingMemberState&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Country code standard ISO-3166-1 of the reporting Member State which have allocated the former national identification code to provide when the national identification code changes (for the first reporting following the change of the national code and any subsequent reporting).</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-008</error_reference>
		<control>The country code exists in the reference table of countries</control>
		<error_message>The country code exists in the reference table of countries</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>25</id>
		<field_name>Old AIFM national identifier - National code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFMNationalCode&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Former national identification code to provide when the national identification code of the AIFM changes (for the first reporting following the change of the national code and any subsequent reporting). The field is mandatory when the  old AIFM national identifier - Reporting Member State is filled in.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-009</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory when the  old AIFM national identifier - Reporting Member State is filled in.</control>
		<error_message>The field is mandatory when the  old AIFM national identifier - Reporting Member State is filled in.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>28</id>
		<field_name>MIC code of the principal market in which the AIFM trades</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;MarketCode&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The “MIC” code (ISO 10383) for trading venues where AIFMs trade. The field is mandatory when the market code type is equal to "MIC" and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-010</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory when the market code type is equal to "MIC" and forbidden otherwise. The MIC code exists in the reference table of markets. ESMA system will not use the validity start date and validity end date of the MIC code to identify the validity of the MIC code.</control>
		<error_message>The MIC code is not correct</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>29</id>
		<field_name>Aggregated value of the principal market in which the AIFM trades</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AggregatedValueAmount&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Aggregated value of the instruments aggregated at the level of the five most important markets in which it trades on behalf of the AIF it manages. Aggregated value expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places. The field is mandatory for market code type different from  “NOT”. The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-011</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for market code type different from  “NOT”.</control>
		<error_message>The field is mandatory for market code type different from  “NOT”.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>30</id>
		<field_name>Aggregated value of the principal market in which the AIFM trades</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AggregatedValueAmount&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Aggregated value of the instruments aggregated at the level of the five most important markets in which it trades on behalf of the AIF it manages. Aggregated value expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places. The field is mandatory for market code type different from  “NOT”. The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-012</error_reference>
		<control>The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on.</control>
		<error_message>The reported value is not consistent with the rank.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>32</id>
		<field_name>Aggregated value of the principal instrument</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AggregatedValueAmount&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Value of the instruments calculated as set out in Article 2 of the Regulation 231/2013 aggregated at the level of the sub-asset type expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places. The value of the instruments should be calculated as of the last business day of the reporting period. The field is mandatory for sub-asset type code different from “NTA_NTA_NOTA” and optional otherwise. The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on. Each rank should be reported once.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-013</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for sub-asset type code different from “NTA_NTA_NOTA” and optional otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The aggregated value is not consistent with the sub-asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id></id>
		<field_name>Aggregated value of the principal instrument</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AggregatedValueAmount&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Value of the instruments calculated as set out in Article 2 of the Regulation 231/2013 aggregated at the level of the sub-asset type expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places. The value of the instruments should be calculated as of the last business day of the reporting period. The field is mandatory for sub-asset type code different from “NTA_NTA_NOTA” and optional otherwise. The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on. Each rank should be reported once.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-014</error_reference>
		<control>The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on.</control>
		<error_message>The reported value is not consistent with the rank.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>35</id>
		<field_name>Total AuM amount in base currency</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AUMAmountInBaseCurrency&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Value in base currency of Assets under management (AuM) for all AIFs managed, (when all AIFs of the AIFM are denominated in one single same base currency that is not the Euro) using the method set out in Articles 2 and 10 of the Regulation 231/2013. The total AuM amount expressed in base currency is filled in without decimal places and when available should be equal to the total AuM amount in Euro * Base currency / EUR FX rate.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-016</error_reference>
		<control>The total AuM amount expressed in base currency should be equal to the total AuM amount in Euro * Base currency / EUR FX rate.</control>
		<error_message>The total AuM amount in base currency is not consistent with the  total AuM amount in Euro.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>35</id>
		<field_name>AIFM Base currency</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;BaseCurrency&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Base currency code (3-character currency code according to the ISO 4217 ) for all AIFs managed by the AIFM.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-017</error_reference>
		<control>The currency code exists in the reference table of countries</control>
		<error_message></error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>38</id>
		<field_name>Base currency / EUR FX reference rate description for no ECB rates</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;FXEUROtherReferenceRateDescription&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Name of the source of the euro reference rates used according to the FX EUR conversion reference rate type reported - Free text for “OTH” type when the corresponding euro reference rate is not published by the ECB - Empty for “ECB” type when the corresponding euro reference rate is published by the ECB The field is mandatory for Base currency / EUR FX reference rate type equal to "OTH" and forbidden otherwise</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAM-020</error_reference>
		<control> The field is mandatory for Base currency / EUR FX reference rate type equal to "OTH" and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The reference rate description is not consistent with the reference rate type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>1</id>
		<field_name>Reporting Member state</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingMemberState&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Country code standard ISO-3166-1 of the Member State to which the AIFM reports the AIFMD reporting.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>FIL-009</error_reference>
		<control>Validate that the reporting member state attribute fits to the file name sender 2 characters of the file</control>
		<error_message>The authority key file attribute is not consistent with the sending</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>2</id>
		<field_name>Reporting Member state</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingMemberState&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Country code standard ISO-3166-1 of the Member State to which the AIFM reports the AIFMD reporting.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>FIL-015</error_reference>
		<control>Check that the reporting member state attribute of the report is listed in the reference table of countries and referenced as EEA country</control>
		<error_message>The authority key file attribute is invalid and should an EU or EEA country</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>4</id>
		<field_name>Filing type</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;FilingType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Flag indicating whether the reporting is an initial filing for the reporting period or an amendment to a previously submitted reporting. The filling types admitted are:   - AMND for "amendment to one reporting previously submitted"   - INIT for "initial reporting for the reporting period"</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-001</error_reference>
		<control>In the file received by ESMA, if for one record, the filing type is equal to “INIT” and that this record has been previously integrated in the ESMA database, the whole record will not be integrated.</control>
		<error_message>The AIF record with "INIT" filing type has been already provided and will not be recorded twice.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>5</id>
		<field_name>AIF content type</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFContentType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Code indicating the contents of the AIF reporting. The AIF content types admitted are:   - 1 for "24(1) reporting obligation"   - 2 for "24(1) + 24(2) reporting obligation"   - 3 for "3(3) (d) reporting obligation"   - 4 for "24(1) + 24(2) + 24(4) reporting obligation"   - 5 for "24(1) + 24(4) reporting obligation" When the AIF no reporting flag is false: The block "AIFPrincipalInfo" will be filled in for all AIF content types. The block "AIFIndividualInfo" will be filled in for AIF content types equal to "2" and "4" The block "AIFLeverageArticle24-2" will be filled in for AIF content types equal to "2" and "4" The block "AIFLeverageArticle24-4" will be filled in for AIF content types equal to "4" and "5"</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-002</error_reference>
		<control>For AIF content type equal to "4" or "5" (24(4) contents), validate that the AIFLeverageArticle24.4 block is reported. When the AIF no reporting flag is false, validate that the AIFPrincipalInfo block is reported. When the AIF no reporting flag is false and AIF content type equal to "2", "4" or "5" (24(2) contents), validate that the AIFIndividualInfo block is reported.</control>
		<error_message>The reported AIF information does not correspond to the AIF content type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>6</id>
		<field_name>Reporting period start date</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingPeriodStartDate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The start date of the reporting period should begin on  the first calendar day of January, April, July or October. yyyy-mm-dd (ISO 8601 Date Format)</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-003</error_reference>
		<control>For quarterly reporting (Q1, Q2, Q3, Q4) Validate that the reporting start date is the beginning of a quarter. Allowed values are YYYY-10-01, YYYY-07-01, YYYY-04-01, YYYY-01-01 For half-yearly reporting (H1, H2) Validate that the reporting start date is the beginning of a half-yearly period (H1, H2) Allowed values are YYYY-07-01, YYYY-01-01 For yearly reporting (Y1) Validate that the reporting start date is the beginning of the calendar year (Y1) Allowed value is YYYY-01-01  Validate that the reporting period start date has the same year that the reporting year.</control>
		<error_message>The reporting period start date is not allowed.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>7</id>
		<field_name>Reporting period end date</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingPeriodEndDate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The end date of the reporting period may be the last calendar day of March, June, September, December or the last day the AIF exists. yyyy-mm-dd (ISO 8601 Date Format)</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-004</error_reference>
		<control>Validate that the reporting end date is less or equal to the end of the last reporting period according to the reporting year and reporting period type. For quarterly reporting (Q1, Q2, Q3, Q4) and reporting year YYYY: Validate that the reporting end date is less or equal to YYYY-03-31 for Q1, YYYY-06-30 for Q2, YYYY-09-30 for Q3, YYYY-12-31 for Q4. For half-yearly reporting (H1, H2) and reporting year YYYY: Validate that the reporting end date is less or equal to YYYY-06-30 for H1,  YYYY-12-31 for H2. For yearly reporting (Y1) and reporting year YYYY: Validate that the reporting end date is less or equal to YYYY-12-31 for Y1.  Validate that the reporting end date is greater than the reporting start date and has the same year.</control>
		<error_message>The reporting period end date is not allowed</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>8</id>
		<field_name>Reporting period type</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingPeriodType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The reporting period types admitted are:    when reporting frequency is quarterly:    - Q1: for 1st quarter of the calendar year    - Q2: for 2nd quarter of the calendar year    - Q3: for 3rd quarter of the calendar year    - Q4: for 4th quarter of the calendar year    when reporting frequency is half yearly:    - H1: for 1st half of the calendar year    - H2: for 2nd half of the calendar year    when reporting frequency is yearly:    - Y1: for the calendar year    when the specific reporting period is from 1st quarter to 3rd quarter due to change in the reporting obligation:    - X1: for period from 1st quarter to 3rd quarter    when the specific reporting period is from 2nd quarter to 4th quarter due to change in the reporting obligation:    - X2: for period from 2nd quarter to 4th quarter For one calendar year, it is not possible to have reporting overlap. Only acceptable subsequent reporting periods are:     - Q1, Q2, Q3, Q4    - Q1, Q2, H2    - Q1, X2    - H1, H2    - H1, Q3, Q4     - Y1    - X1, Q4</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-005</error_reference>
		<control>For one specific calendar year and AIF, it is not possible to have reporting overlap. It is not possible to be reported with:    - H1 and Q1    - H1 and Q2    - H2 and Q3    - H2 and Q4    - Y1 and Q1    - Y1 and Q2    - Y1 and Q3    - Y1 and Q4    - Y1 and H1    - Y1 and H2</control>
		<error_message>Data have been reported twice for the same reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>12</id>
		<field_name>Change in AIF reporting obligation Quarter</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFReportingObligationChangeQuarter&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>
			Code indicating the quarter during which the frequency and/or contents reporting obligation on the AIF changes. The codes for the reporting obligation change quarter are:    - Q1: for 1st quarter of the calendar year    - Q2: for 2nd quarter of the calendar year    - Q3: for 3rd quarter of the calendar year    - Q4: for 4th quarter of the calendar year The field is mandatoty for
			&lt;AIFReportingObligationChangeFrequencyCode&gt;
				or
				&lt;AIFReportingObligationChangeContentsCode&gt; filled in and forbidden otherwise.
		</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-006</error_reference>
		<control>
			The field is mandatory for
			&lt;AIFReportingObligationChangeFrequencyCode&gt;
				or
				&lt;AIFReportingObligationChangeContentsCode&gt; filled in
		</control>
		<error_message>The quarter for the AIF reporting obligation change should be reported</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>16</id>
		<field_name>AIFM National Code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFMNationalCode&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Unique reference identifying each AIFM allocated by the national competent authority  of the reporting Member State of the AIFM to which the AIFM reports under AIFMD</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-007</error_reference>
		<control>The AIFM national code exists in the ESMA register for the reporting Member State</control>
		<error_message>The AIFM national code does not exist in the AIFM reference table.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>17</id>
		<field_name>AIF national code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFNationalCode&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Unique reference identifying each AIFallocated by the national competent authority of the reporting Member State of the AIFM to which the AIFM reports under AIFMD</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-008</error_reference>
		<control>The AIF national code exists in the ESMA register for the reported AIFM and for the reporting Member State</control>
		<error_message>The AIF national code does not exist in the AIF reference table.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>19</id>
		<field_name>AIF EEA Flag</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFEEAFlag&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Flag indicating whether the AIF is domiciled in the EEA or the EU. true for EEA or EU AIFs false for non-EEA or EU AIFs</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-009</error_reference>
		<control>The AIF domicile should belong to the EEA or EU area when the AIF EEA flag is true.</control>
		<error_message>The EEA flag is not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>21</id>
		<field_name>Domicile of the AIF</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFDomicile&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>For EU AIFs, the domicile of the AIF should be understood as the home Member State of the AIF as defined in Article 4(1)(p) of the AIFMD. For non-EU AIFs, the domicile of the AIF should be the country where the AIF is authorised or registered or where it has its registered office. Country code standard ISO-3166-1</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-010</error_reference>
		<control>The country code exists in the reference table of countries</control>
		<error_message>The domicile of the AIF is not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>22</id>
		<field_name>Inception Date</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;InceptionDate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The date the AIF started business (yyyy-mm-dd (ISO 8601 Date Format)). The inception date should not be after the start date of the reporting period.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-011</error_reference>
		<control>The inception date should be before the reporting period start date.</control>
		<error_message>The inception date is not allowed as it should be before the reporting start date</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>23</id>
		<field_name>AIF no reporting flag</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFNoReportingFlag&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>true for empty file (no information to report for the reporting period) false otherwise The AIFCompleteDescription block will not be filled in when the AIF no reporting flag is true.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-012</error_reference>
		<control>The AIFCompleteDescription block is not filled in when the AIF no reporting flag is true.</control>
		<error_message>The AIF no reporting flag is not consistent with the reported information.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>24</id>
		<field_name>AIF LEI code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFIdentifierLEI&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Legal Entity Identifer (LEI) (ISO 17442 standard) of the Entity  or if not available the Interim Entity Identifier (IEI): •Characters 1-4: A four character prefix allocated uniquely to each LOU. •Characters 5-6: Two reserved characters set to zero. •Characters 7-18: Entity - specific part of the code generated and assigned by LOUs according to transparent, sound and robust allocation policies. •Characters 19-20: Two check digits</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-013</error_reference>
		<control>Verify the correctness of the LEI code format rules following the calculation methodology of the 2-last check digits under validation rules using ISO 7064, Data Processing, Check Character Systems.</control>
		<error_message>The check digits of the LEI code are not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>25</id>
		<field_name>AIF ISIN code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFIdentifierISIN&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>ISIN code (ISO 6166 standard)</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-014</error_reference>
		<control>Verify the correctness of the ISIN code format rules following the calculation methodology of the last check digit</control>
		<error_message>The check digit of the ISIN code is not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>31</id>
		<field_name>Old AIF national identifier - Reporting Member State</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingMemberState&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Country code standard ISO-3166-1 of the reporting Member State to which the AIFM reports under AIFMD when the national code identifying the AIF has been modified. The field is mandatory when the old AIF national identifier - National code is filled in.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-015</error_reference>
		<control>The country code should exist in the reference table of countries and should be referenced as EEA country.</control>
		<error_message>The country of the old AIF national code is not correct and should be an EEA or EU country.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>34</id>
		<field_name>Share class national code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ShareClassNationalCode&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Where available, unique reference allocated by the national competent authority to which the AIFM reports under AIFMD identifying each share class  The field is forbidden for AIF share class equal to false and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-016</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for AIF share class equal to false and optional otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The share class national code is not consistent with the share class flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>35</id>
		<field_name>Share class ISIN code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ShareClassIdentifierISIN&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Where available, the ISIN code (ISO 6166 standard) identifying each share class. The field is forbidden for AIF share class equal to false and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-017</error_reference>
		<control>Verify the correctness of the ISIN code format rules following the calculation methodology of the last check digit</control>
		<error_message>The check digit of the ISIN code is not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>36</id>
		<field_name>Share class ISIN code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ShareClassIdentifierISIN&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Where available, the ISIN code (ISO 6166 standard) identifying each share class. The field is forbidden for AIF share class equal to false and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-018</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for AIF share class equal to false and optional otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The share class ISIN code is not consistent with the share class flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>36</id>
		<field_name>Share class SEDOL code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ShareClassIdentifierSEDOL&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Where available, the CUSIP code identifying each share class. The field is forbidden for AIF share class equal to false and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-019</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for AIF share class equal to false and optional otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The share class SEDOL code is not consistent with the share class flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>37</id>
		<field_name>Share class CUSIP code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ShareClassIdentifierCUSIP&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Where available, the SEDOL code identifying each share class. The field is forbidden for AIF share class equal to false and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-020</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for AIF share class equal to false and optional otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The share class CUSIP code is not consistent with the share class flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>38</id>
		<field_name>Share class Bloomberg code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ShareClassIdentifierTicker&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Where available, the Bloomberg ticker symbol identifying each share class. The field is forbidden for AIF share class equal to false and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-021</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for AIF share class equal to false and optional otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The share class Bloomberg code is not consistent with the share class flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>39</id>
		<field_name>Share class Reuters code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ShareClassIdentifierRIC&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Where available, the Reuters Identifier Code (RIC) identifying each share class. The field is forbidden for AIF share class equal to false and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-022</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for AIF share class equal to false and optional otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The share class Reuters code is not consistent with the share class flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>40</id>
		<field_name>Share class name</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ShareClassName&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The name of the share class. The field is mandatory for AIF share class equal to true and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-023</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for AIF share class equal to true and Forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The share class name is not consistent with the share class flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>42</id>
		<field_name>Master AIF name</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFName&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>No standard. It is strongly recommended to provide the full name as provided by Swift for master AIF(s) that have one BIC or LEI code. The field is mandatoty for Master feeder status equal to "FEEDER" and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-024</error_reference>
		<control>The field is optional for Master feeder status equal to "FEEDER" and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The master AIF name is not consistent with the master feeder status.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>43</id>
		<field_name>Master AIF national identifier - Reporting Member State</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingMemberState&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Country code standard ISO-3166-1 of the reporting Member State to which the AIFM of the master AIF(s) reports under AIFMD The field is optional for Master feeder status equal to "FEEDER" and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-025</error_reference>
		<control>The country code should exist in the reference table of countries and should be referenced as EEA country</control>
		<error_message>The country of the master AIF national code is not correct and should be an EEA or EU country.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>44</id>
		<field_name>Master AIF national identifier - Reporting Member State</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ReportingMemberState&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Country code standard ISO-3166-1 of the reporting Member State to which the AIFM of the master AIF(s) reports under AIFMD The field is optional for Master feeder status equal to "FEEDER" and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-026</error_reference>
		<control>The field is optional for Master feeder status equal to "FEEDER" and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The master AIF name is not consistent with the master feeder status.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>44</id>
		<field_name>Master AIF national identifier - National code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIFNationalCode&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Unique reference identifying the master AIF allocated by the national competent authority to which the AIFM of the master AIF (s) reports under AIFMD The field is optional for Master feeder status equal to "FEEDER" and forbidden otherwise. The field is mandatory when the master AIF national identifier - Reporting Member State is filled in.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-027</error_reference>
		<control>The field is optional for Master feeder status equal to "FEEDER" and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The master AIF national code is not consistent with the master feeder status.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>46</id>
		<field_name>Prime Broker LEI code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationLEI&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>LEI code (ISO 17442 standard) or if not available the interim entity identifier: Characters 1-4: A four character prefix allocated uniquely to each LOU. •Characters 5-6: Two reserved characters set to zero. •Characters 7-18: Entity - specific part of the code generated and assigned by LOUs according to transparent, sound and robust allocation policies. •Characters 19-20: Two check digits</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-028</error_reference>
		<control>Verify the correctness of the LEI code format rules following the calculation methodology of the 2-last check digits under validation rules using ISO 7064, Data Processing, Check Character Systems.</control>
		<error_message>The check digits of the LEI code are not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>49</id>
		<field_name>Base currency of the AIF</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;BaseCurrency&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Currency code (3-character currency code according to the ISO 4217 ) used for reporting the information. Only one currency should be reported. This means that AIFs with several share classes denominated in different currencies should have only one base currency.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-029</error_reference>
		<control>The currency code exists in the reference table of currencies</control>
		<error_message>The currency code is not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>50</id>
		<field_name>Base currency / EUR FX rate</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;FXEURRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Conversion rate filled in with 4 decimal places. The field is mandatory for AIF base currency different from EUR and forbidden otherwise</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-030</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for AIF base currency different from EUR and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The FX rate is not consistent with the AIF base currency.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>51</id>
		<field_name>Base currency / EUR FX reference rate type</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;FXEURReferenceRateType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>2 types are admitted: - “ECB” when the base currency is one of the currencies for which the exchange rates are euro reference rates published by the ECB - “OTH” in other cases  The field is mandatory for AIF base currency different from EUR and forbidden otherwise. The ECB reference rates are published daily when TARGET system is open.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-031</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for AIF base currency different from EUR and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The FX reference rate type is not consistent with the AIF base currency.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>52</id>
		<field_name>Base currency / EUR FX reference rate description for no ECB rates</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;FXEUROtherReferenceRateDescription&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Name of the source of the euro reference rates used according to the FX EUR conversion reference rate type indicated in item X - Free text for “OTH” type when the corresponding euro reference rate is not published by the ECB - Empty for “ECB” type when the corresponding euro reference rate is published by the ECB</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-032</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for reference rate type equal to "OTH" and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The reference rate description is not consistent with the  FX reference rate type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>54</id>
		<field_name>First funding source country</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;FirstFundingSourceCountry&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The country of the first main funding source (counterparty of the liability) using the country code standard ISO-3166-1.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-033</error_reference>
		<control>The country code exists in the reference table of countries</control>
		<error_message>The first funding country is not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>55</id>
		<field_name>Second funding source country</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;SecondFundingSourceCountry&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The country of the second main funding source (counterparty of the liability) using the country code standard ISO-3166-1.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-034</error_reference>
		<control>The country code exists in the reference table of countries</control>
		<error_message>The second funding country is not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>56</id>
		<field_name>Third funding source country</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ThirdFundingSourceCountry&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The country of the third main funding source (counterparty of the liability) using the country code standard ISO-3166-1.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-035</error_reference>
		<control>The country code exists in the reference table of countries</control>
		<error_message>The third funding country is not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>58</id>
		<field_name>Investment strategy code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;HedgeFundStrategyType&gt; &lt;PrivateEquityFundStrategyType&gt; &lt;FundOfFundsStrategyType&gt; &lt;OtherFundStrategyType&gt; &lt;RealEstateFundStrategyType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>
			The investment strategy types admitted are listed in Annex II - Table 3. Investment strategies are mutually exclusive, except when AIFMs select 'None'. Within the
			&lt;HedgeFundStrategyType&gt;
				block, if the investment strategy code "MULT_HFND" is reported, at least 2 other different hedge fund investment strategy codes should be reported. Within the
				&lt;PrivateEquityFundStrategyType&gt;
					block, if the investment strategy code "MULT_PEQF" is reported, at least 2 other different Private equity fund investment strategy codes should be reported. Within the
					&lt;RealEstateFundStrategyType&gt; block, if the investment strategy code "MULT_PEQF" is reported, at least 2 other different Private equity fund investment strategy codes should be reported.		
		</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-036</error_reference>
		<control>
			Check that: - For predominant AIF type "HFND", the
			&lt;HedgeFundStrategyTypeType&gt;
				block is reported - For predominant AIF type "PEQF", the
				&lt;PrivateEquityFundStrategyType&gt;
					block is reported - For predominant AIF type "RESF", the
					&lt;RealEstateFundStrategyType&gt;
						block is reported - For predominant AIF type "FOFS", the
						&lt;FundOfFundsStrategyType&gt;
							block is reported - For predominant AIF type "OTHR", the
							&lt;OtherFundStrategyType&gt; block is reported
		</control>
		<error_message>The investment strategy code is not consistent with the predominant AIF type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>59</id>
		<field_name>Investment strategy code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;HedgeFundStrategyType&gt; &lt;PrivateEquityFundStrategyType&gt; &lt;FundOfFundsStrategyType&gt; &lt;OtherFundStrategyType&gt; &lt;RealEstateFundStrategyType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>
			The investment strategy types admitted are listed in Annex II - Table 3. Investment strategies are mutually exclusive, except when AIFMs select 'None'. Within the
			&lt;HedgeFundStrategyType&gt;
				block, if the investment strategy code "MULT_HFND" is reported, at least 2 other different hedge fund investment strategy codes should be reported. Within the
				&lt;PrivateEquityFundStrategyType&gt;
					block, if the investment strategy code "MULT_PEQF" is reported, at least 2 other different Private equity fund investment strategy codes should be reported. Within the
					&lt;RealEstateFundStrategyType&gt; block, if the investment strategy code "MULT_PEQF" is reported, at least 2 other different Private equity fund investment strategy codes should be reported.
		</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-037</error_reference>
		<control>
			Check that: - Different Investment strategies are not reported when the AIF predominant type is different from "NONE. In that case, only one investment strategy block (HedgeFundInvestmentStrategies, PrivateEquityFundInvestmentStrategies, RealEstateFundInvestmentStrategies, FundOfFundsInvestmentStrategies, OtherFundInvestmentStrategies) can be reported as the investment strategies are mutually exclusive..   - Within the
			&lt;HedgeFundStrategyType&gt;
				block, if the investment strategy code "MULT_HFND" is reported, at least 2 other different hedge fund investment strategy codes should be reported. - Within the
				&lt;PrivateEquityFundStrategyType&gt;
					block, if the investment strategy code "MULT_PEQF" is reported, at least 2 other different Private equity fund investment strategy codes should be reported. - Within the
					&lt;RealEstateFundStrategyType&gt; block, if the investment strategy code "MULT_PEQF" is reported, at least 2 other different Private equity fund investment strategy codes should be reported.
		</control>
		<error_message>The investment strategy code is not allowed.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>59</id>
		<field_name>Primary strategy flag</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;PrimarystrategyFlag&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Flag indicating whether the fund strategy is the primary strategy. There is only one primary investment strategy. true for primary strategy false otherwise The flag should be true when the investment strategy code reported is equal to "MULT_PEQF", "MULT_HFND" or "MULT_REST".</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-038</error_reference>
		<control>The flag should be true when the investment strategy code reported is equal to "MULT_PEQF", "MULT_HFND" or "MULT_REST".</control>
		<error_message>Multi strategies investment strategies should be primary strategies.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>60</id>
		<field_name>Investment strategy NAV percentage </field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;StrategyNAVRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>NAV rate expressed as a percentage for each reported investment strategy. As there is no Nav percentages reported for multi strategies funds, this element is only mandatory for investment strategy codes different from "MULT_PEQF", "MULT_HFND" or "MULT_REST". The sum of all the percentages should be 100%</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-039</error_reference>
		<control> For the reported AIF, the sum of all the reported investment strategy NAV percentages should be 100%</control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>61</id>
		<field_name>Investment strategy NAV percentage </field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;StrategyNAVRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>NAV rate expressed as a percentage for each reported investment strategy. As there is no Nav percentages reported for multi strategies funds, this element is only mandatory for investment strategy codes different from "MULT_PEQF", "MULT_HFND" or "MULT_REST". The sum of all the percentages should be 100%</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-040</error_reference>
		<control>The NAV percentage is forbidden when the investment strategy code reported is equal to "MULT_PEQF", "MULT_HFND" or "MULT_REST".</control>
		<error_message>There is no NAV percentage reported for multi strategies investment strategies.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>61</id>
		<field_name>Description for strategy type Other</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;StrategyTypeOtherDescription&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>No standard. The field is mandatory for strategy types equal to: -  “OTHR_HFND”  (Other hedge fund strategy) -  “OTHR_PEQF” (Other private equity fund strategy) -  “OTHR_REST” (Other real estate strategy) -  “OTHR_FOFS” (Other fund of funds) -  “OTHR_OTHF” (Other fund)</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-041</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for investement strategy codes equal to: -  “OTHR_HFND” -  “OTHR_PRIV” -  “OTHR_REST” -  “OTHR_FOFS” -  “OTHR_OTHF”</control>
		<error_message>The investement strategy code description is not consistent with the reported investment strategy code.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>66</id>
		<field_name>Instrument code type of the five main instruments in which the AIF is trading</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;InstrumentCodeType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The instrument code type admitted are: - “NONE” for instrument without codes - “ISIN” for instruments with ISIN codes - “AII” for instruments with AII codes The field is mandatory for Sub-asset type code different from “NTA_NTA_NOTA” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-042</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for sub-asset type code different from “NTA_NTA_NOTA” and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The instrument code type is not consistent with the sub-asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>67</id>
		<field_name>Instrument name of the five main instruments in which the AIF is trading</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;InstrumentName&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>No standard. It is strongly recommended to provide the instrument short name as provided by Swift under ISO18774 when available. The field is mandatory for Sub-asset type code different from “NTA_NTA_NOTA” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-043</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for sub-asset type code different from “NTA_NTA_NOTA” and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The instrument name is not consistent with the sub-asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>68</id>
		<field_name>Instrument ISIN code of the five main instruments in which the AIF is trading</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ISINInstrumentIdentification&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The ISIN code of the instrument (ISO 6166 standard) when available. The field is mandatory for Instrument code type code equal to "ISIN" and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-044</error_reference>
		<control>Verify the correctness of the ISIN code format rules following the calculation methodology of the last check digit</control>
		<error_message>The check digit of the ISIN code is not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id></id>
		<field_name></field_name>
		<element_name></element_name>
		<technical_guidance></technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-045</error_reference>
		<control> The field is mandatory for Instrument code type equal to "ISIN" and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The instrument ISIN code is not consistent with the instrument code type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>69</id>
		<field_name>AII exchange code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIIExchangeCode&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Four character MIC of the market that admits the derivative to trading. The field is mandatory for Instrument code type equal to "AII" and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-046</error_reference>
		<control>The MIC code exists in the reference table of markets. ESMA system will not use the validity start date and validity end date of the MIC code to identify the validity of the MIC code.</control>
		<error_message>The MIC code is not correct</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id></id>
		<field_name></field_name>
		<element_name></element_name>
		<technical_guidance></technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-047</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for Instrument code type equal to "AII" and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The instrument AII exchange code is not consistent with the instrument code type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>70</id>
		<field_name>AII exchange product code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIIProductCode&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>A code that is uniquely associated with a particular underlying instrument and settlement type and other characteristics of the contract. It is between one and 12 characters in length. The field is mandatory for Instrument code type equal to "AII" and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>
			CAF-048
			</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for Instrument code type equal to "AII" and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The instrument AII exchange product code is not consistent with the instrument code type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>71</id>
		<field_name>AII derivative type</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIIDerivativeType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>This is a single character field identifying whether the instrument is an option (O) or a future (F). The field is mandatory for Instrument code type equal to "AII" and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-049</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for Instrument code type equal to "AII" and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The instrument AII derivative type is not consistent with the instrument code type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>72</id>
		<field_name>AII Put/Call identifier</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIIPutCallIdentifier&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>This is a single character field identifying whether the option (if it is an option) is a put (P)or a call (C). F in case of a future. The field is mandatory for Instrument code type equal to "AII" and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-050</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for Instrument code type equal to "AII" and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The instrument put/call identifier is not consistent with the instrument code type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>73</id>
		<field_name>AII expiry/delivery/prompt date</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIIExpiryDate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Exercise date/ maturity date of a derivative contract. The field is mandatory for Instrument code type equal to "AII" and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-051</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for Instrument code type equal to "AII" and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The instrument AII expiry date is not consistent with the instrument code type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>74</id>
		<field_name> AII strike price</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AIIStrikePrice&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The strike price of an option or other financial instrument. In case of a future the strike should contain the value "0‟. The field is mandatory for Instrument code type equal to "AII" and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-052</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for Instrument code type equal to "AII" and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The instrument AII strike price is not consistent with the instrument code type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>75</id>
		<field_name>Position type of the five main instruments in which the AIF is trading</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;PositionType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The long/short position flag admitted are: - “L” for long - “S” for short The field is mandatory for Sub-asset type code different from “NTA_NTA_NOTA” and forbidden otherwise</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-053</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for sub-asset type code different from “NTA_NTA_NOTA” and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The position type is not consistent with the sub-asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>76</id>
		<field_name>Instrument position value of the five main instruments in which the AIF is trading</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;PositionValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Instrument position value  expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places. The field is mandatory for sub-asset type code different from “NTA_NTA_NOTA” and forbidden otherwise</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-054</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for sub-asset type code different from “NTA_NTA_NOTA” and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The position value is not consistent with the sub-asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>77</id>
		<field_name>Instrument position value of the five main instruments in which the AIF is trading</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;PositionValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Instrument position value  expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places. The field is mandatory for sub-asset type code different from “NTA_NTA_NOTA” and forbidden otherwise</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-055</error_reference>
		<control>The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on.</control>
		<error_message>The reported value is not consistent with the rank.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>77</id>
		<field_name>Short position hedging percentage *</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ShortPositionHedgingRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>For short positions, indication of whether the position is used to hedge a position with a similar economic exposure. The field is optional for PositionType equal to “S” and forbidden otherwise</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-056</error_reference>
		<control>The field is optional for position type equal to “S” and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The position value is not consistent with the position type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>78</id>
		<field_name>Africa NAV percentage</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AfricaNAVRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>NAV rate expressed as a percentage for each geographical area. Certain regions may have negative values whereas other regions may have values above 100%. The sum of all the region percentages should be 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-057</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of all the area NAV percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>79</id>
		<field_name>Asia Pacific (other than Middle East) NAV percentage</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AsiaPacificNAVRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>NAV rate expressed as a percentage for each geographical area. Certain regions may have negative values whereas other regions may have values above 100%. The sum of all the region percentages should be 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-057</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of all the area NAV percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>80</id>
		<field_name>Europe (other than EEA) NAV percentage</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EuropeNAVRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>NAV rate expressed as a percentage for each geographical area. Certain regions may have negative values whereas other regions may have values above 100%. The sum of all the region percentages should be 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-057</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of all the area NAV percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>81</id>
		<field_name>Europe EEA NAV percentage</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EEANAVRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>NAV rate expressed as a percentage for each geographical area. Certain regions may have negative values whereas other regions may have values above 100%. The sum of all the region percentages should be 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-057</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of all the area NAV percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>82</id>
		<field_name>Middle East NAV percentage</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;MiddleEastNAVRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>NAV rate expressed as a percentage for each geographical area. Certain regions may have negative values whereas other regions may have values above 100%. The sum of all the region percentages should be 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-057</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of all the area NAV percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>83</id>
		<field_name>North America NAV percentage</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;NorthAmericaNAVRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>NAV rate expressed as a percentage for each geographical area. Certain regions may have negative values whereas other regions may have values above 100%. The sum of all the region percentages should be 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-057</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of all the area NAV percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>84</id>
		<field_name>South America NAV percentage</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;SouthAmericaNAVRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>NAV rate expressed as a percentage for each geographical area. Certain regions may have negative values whereas other regions may have values above 100%. The sum of all the region percentages should be 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-057</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of all the area NAV percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>85</id>
		<field_name>Supra National/Multiple regions NAV percentage</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;SupraNationalNAVRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>NAV rate expressed as a percentage for each geographical area. Certain regions may have negative values whereas other regions may have values above 100%. The sum of all the region percentages should be 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-057</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of all the area NAV percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>86</id>
		<field_name>Africa AuM value percentage *</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AfricaAUMRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>AUM rate expressed as a percentage for each geographical area. The sum of all the area percentages should be 100%</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-058</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of all the area AUM percentages should be equel to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>87</id>
		<field_name>Asia Pacific (other than Middle East) AuM value percentage *</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AsiaPacificAUMRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>AUM rate expressed as a percentage for each geographical area. The sum of all the area percentages should be 100%</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-058</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of all the area AUM percentages should be equel to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>88</id>
		<field_name>Europe (other than EEA) AuM value percentage *</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EuropeAUMRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>AUM rate expressed as a percentage for each geographical area. The sum of all the area percentages should be 100%</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-058</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of all the area AUM percentages should be equel to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>89</id>
		<field_name>Europe EEA AuM value percentage *</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EEAAUMRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>AUM rate expressed as a percentage for each geographical area. The sum of all the area percentages should be 100%</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-058</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of all the area AUM percentages should be equel to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>90</id>
		<field_name>Middle East AuM value percentage *</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;MiddleEastAUMRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>AUM rate expressed as a percentage for each geographical area. The sum of all the area percentages should be 100%</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-058</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of all the area AUM percentages should be equel to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>91</id>
		<field_name>North America AuM value percentage *</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;NorthAmericaAUMRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>AUM rate expressed as a percentage for each geographical area. The sum of all the area percentages should be 100%</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-058</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of all the area AUM percentages should be equel to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>92</id>
		<field_name>South America AuM value percentage *</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;SouthAmericaAUMRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>AUM rate expressed as a percentage for each geographical area. The sum of all the area percentages should be 100%</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-058</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of all the area AUM percentages should be equel to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>93</id>
		<field_name>Supra National/Multiple regions AuM value percentage *</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;SupraNationalAUMRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>AUM rate expressed as a percentage for each geographical area. The sum of all the area percentages should be 100%</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-058</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of all the area AUM percentages should be equel to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>96</id>
		<field_name>Sub-asset type of the 10 principal exposures</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;SubAssetType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The ten sub-asset types of the ten principal exposures. The sub-asset types admitted are listed in Annex II - Table 1  (i.e. highest level of detail available). The field is mandatory for macro asset type code different from “NTA” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-059</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for macro asset type code different from “NTA” and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The sub-asset type is not consistent with the macro-asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>97</id>
		<field_name>Position type of the 10 principal exposures</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;PositionType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The long/short position flag admitted are: - “L” for long - “S” for short  The field is mandatory for macro asset type code different from “NTA” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-060</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for macro asset type code different from “NTA” and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The position type is not consistent with the macro-asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>98</id>
		<field_name>Aggregated value of the 10 principal exposures</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AggregatedValueAmount&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Aggregated value for each sub-asset type expressed in Base currency filled in without decimal places. The field is mandatory for macro asset type code different from “NTA” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-061</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for macro asset type code different from “NTA” and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The aggregated value is not consistent with the macro-asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id></id>
		<field_name></field_name>
		<element_name></element_name>
		<technical_guidance></technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-062</error_reference>
		<control>The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on.</control>
		<error_message>The reported value is not consistent with the rank.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>99</id>
		<field_name>Aggregated value percentage of the 10 principal exposures</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AggregatedValueRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Aggregated value rate expressed as a percentage for each sub-asset type. The field is mandatory for macro asset type code different from “NTA” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-063</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for macro asset type code different from “NTA” and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The aggregated value percentage is not consistent with the macro-asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>101</id>
		<field_name>Counterparty LEI code of the 10 principal exposures</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationLEI&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Legal Entity Identifer (LEI) (ISO 17442 standard) of the Entity  or if not available the Interim Entity Identifier (IEI): •Characters 1-4: A four character prefix allocated uniquely to each LOU. •Characters 5-6: Two reserved characters set to zero. •Characters 7-18: Entity - specific part of the code generated and assigned by LOUs according to transparent, sound and robust allocation policies. •Characters 19-20: Two check digits The LEI code cannot be filled if the counterparty name is not filled in. </technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-064</error_reference>
		<control>The LEI code cannot be filled if the counterparty name is not filled in.</control>
		<error_message>The LEI code is not consistent with the counterparty name.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>102</id>
		<field_name>Counterparty LEI code of the 10 principal exposures</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationLEI&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Legal Entity Identifer (LEI) (ISO 17442 standard) of the Entity  or if not available the Interim Entity Identifier (IEI): •Characters 1-4: A four character prefix allocated uniquely to each LOU. •Characters 5-6: Two reserved characters set to zero. •Characters 7-18: Entity - specific part of the code generated and assigned by LOUs according to transparent, sound and robust allocation policies. •Characters 19-20: Two check digits The LEI code cannot be filled if the counterparty name is not filled in. </technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-065</error_reference>
		<control>Verify the correctness of the LEI code format rules following the calculation methodology of the 2-last check digits under validation rules using ISO 7064, Data Processing, Check Character Systems.</control>
		<error_message>The check digits of the LEI code are not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>102</id>
		<field_name>Counterparty BIC code of the 10 principal exposures</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationBIC&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>BIC code of the entity (ISO 9362 standard) The BIC code cannot be filled if the counterparty name is not filled in. </technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-066</error_reference>
		<control>The BIC code cannot be filled if the counterparty name is not filled in.</control>
		<error_message>The BIC code is not consistent with the counterparty name.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>105</id>
		<field_name>Position type  for portfolio concentration</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;PositionType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The long/short position flag admitted are: - “L” for long - “S” for short  The field is mandatory for asset type code different from “NTA_NTA” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-067</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for asset type code different from “NTA_NTA” and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The position type is not consistent with the asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>106</id>
		<field_name>Market code type for portfolio concentration</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;MarketCodeType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The market codes types admitted are:     - MIC for markets with MIC codes     - OTC for OTC derivatives     - XXX for no market</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-068</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for asset type code different from “NTA_NTA” and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The market code type is not consistent with the asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>107</id>
		<field_name>Market code for portfolio concentration</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;MarketCode&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The “MIC” code (ISO 10383) for the trading venue where the category of investment is traded. The field is mandatory for market type code equal to “MIC” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-069</error_reference>
		<control>The MIC code exists in the reference table of markets. ESMA system will not use the validity start date and validity end date of the MIC code to identify the validity of the MIC code.</control>
		<error_message>The MIC code is not correct</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id></id>
		<field_name></field_name>
		<element_name></element_name>
		<technical_guidance></technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-070</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for market type code equal to “MIC” and forbidden otherwise. </control>
		<error_message>The MIC code is not consistent with the market code type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>108</id>
		<field_name>Asset aggregated value  for portfolio concentration</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AggregatedValueAmount&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Aggregated value for each each asset type, market and position type expressed in Base currency filled in without decimal places. The field is mandatory for asset type code different from “NTA_NTA” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-071</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for asset type code different from “NTA_NTA” and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The aggregated value is not consistent with the asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>109</id>
		<field_name>Asset aggregated value  for portfolio concentration</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AggregatedValueAmount&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Aggregated value for each each asset type, market and position type expressed in Base currency filled in without decimal places. The field is mandatory for asset type code different from “NTA_NTA” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-072</error_reference>
		<control>The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on.</control>
		<error_message>The reported value is not consistent with the rank.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>109</id>
		<field_name>Asset aggregated value percentage for portfolio concentration</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AggregatedValueRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Aggregated value rate expressed as a percentage for each each asset type, market and position type . The field is mandatory for asset type code different from “NTA_NTA” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-073</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for asset type code different from “NTA_NTA” and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The aggregated value percentage is not consistent with the asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>110</id>
		<field_name>Counterparty name for portfolio concentration</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityName&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Entity name. (no standard) It is strongly recommended to provide the full name corresponding to the allocated LEI code (or BIC code if any and LEI not available). Counterparty data is not allowed when reported market type is different from “OTC".</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-074</error_reference>
		<control>Counterparty data is not allowed when reported market is different from market code type “OTC”.</control>
		<error_message>The counterparty name is not consistent with the market code type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>111</id>
		<field_name>Counterparty LEI code  for portfolio concentration</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationLEI&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>LEI code (ISO 17442 standard) or if not available the interim entity identifier: Characters 1-4: A four character prefix allocated uniquely to each LOU. •Characters 5-6: Two reserved characters set to zero. •Characters 7-18: Entity - specific part of the code generated and assigned by LOUs according to transparent, sound and robust allocation policies. •Characters 19-20: Two check digits Counterparty data is not allowed when reported market type is different from “OTC". The LEI code cannot be filled if the counterparty name is not filled in.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-075</error_reference>
		<control>The LEI code cannot be filled if the counterparty name is not filled in.</control>
		<error_message>The LEI code is not consistent with the counterparty name.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id></id>
		<field_name></field_name>
		<element_name></element_name>
		<technical_guidance></technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-076</error_reference>
		<control>Verify the correctness of the LEI code format rules following the calculation methodology of the 2-last check digits under validation rules using ISO 7064, Data Processing, Check Character Systems.</control>
		<error_message>The counterparty LEI code is not consistent with the counterparty name.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>112</id>
		<field_name>Counterparty BIC code for portfolio concentration</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationBIC&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>BIC code (ISO 9362 standard) Counterparty data is not allowed when reported market type is different from “OTC". The BIC code cannot be filled if the counterparty name is not filled in.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-077</error_reference>
		<control>The BIC code cannot be filled if the counterparty name is not filled in.</control>
		<error_message>The BIC code is not consistent with the counterparty name.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id></id>
		<field_name></field_name>
		<element_name></element_name>
		<technical_guidance></technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-078</error_reference>
		<control>Counterparty data is not allowed when reported market is different from “OTC”.</control>
		<error_message>The counterparty BIC code is not consistent with the counterparty name.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>113</id>
		<field_name>Position size type</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;TypicalPositionSize&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The category of deal/position size that the private equity fund typically invests in. The possible categories are:  - V_SMALL for "Very Small" when less than €5m  - SMALL for "Small" when between €5m to €25m  - LOW_MID_MKT for "Low mid market" when between €25m to €150m  - UP_MID_MKT for "Upper mid market" when between €150m to €500m  - L_CAP for "Large cap" when between €500m to €1bn  - M_CAP for "Mega cap" when for €1bn and greater See Annex II - Table 4. The field is mandatory for AIF predominant type “Private Equity funds” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-079</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for AIF predominant type “Private Equity funds” and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The position size type is not consistent with the predominant AIF type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>116</id>
		<field_name>MIC code of principal market in which AIF trades</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;MarketCode&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The “MIC” code (ISO 10383) for the trading venue. The field is mandatory for market type code equal to “MIC” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-080</error_reference>
		<control>The MIC code exists in the reference table of markets. ESMA system will not use the validity start date and validity end date of the MIC code to identify the validity of the MIC code.</control>
		<error_message>The MIC code is not correct</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>117</id>
		<field_name>MIC code of principal market in which AIF trades</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;MarketCode&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The “MIC” code (ISO 10383) for the trading venue. The field is mandatory for market type code equal to “MIC” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-081</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for market type code equal to “MIC” and forbidden otherwise.  </control>
		<error_message>The MIC code is not consistent with the market code type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>117</id>
		<field_name>Aggregated value of principal market in which AIF trades</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AggregatedValueAmount&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Aggregated value of the instruments aggregated at the level of the three most important markets in which the AIF trades. Aggregated value expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places.The field is mandatory for market type code different from “NOT” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-082</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for market type code different from “NOT” and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The aggregated value is not consistent with the market code type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>118</id>
		<field_name>Aggregated value of principal market in which AIF trades</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AggregatedValueAmount&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Aggregated value of the instruments aggregated at the level of the three most important markets in which the AIF trades. Aggregated value expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places.The field is mandatory for market type code different from “NOT” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-083</error_reference>
		<control>The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on.</control>
		<error_message>The reported value is not consistent with the rank.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>119</id>
		<field_name>Investor Concentration percentage by professional clients</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ProfessionalInvestorConcentrationRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Rate expressed as a percentage. The sum of the percentages reported by professional clients and retail investors should be 100%  </technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-084</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the percentages reported by professional clients and retail investors should be 100%  or 0%. The retail investor rate and professional investor rate should be filled in with 0% when there is no information to report. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 0% or 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>120</id>
		<field_name>Investor Concentration percentage by retail investors </field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RetailInvestorConcentrationRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Rate expressed as a percentage. The sum of the percentages reported by professional clients and retail investors should be 100%  </technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-084</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the percentages reported by professional clients and retail investors should be 100%  or 0%. The retail investor rate and professional investor rate should be filled in with 0% when there is no information to report.</control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 0% or 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>122</id>
		<field_name>Gross value of individual exposure</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;GrossValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Gross value amount for Sub-asset types "DER_FEX_INVT", "DER_FEX_HEDG" and "DER_IRD_INTR" expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-085</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for sub-asset type different from "DER_FEX_INVT", "DER_FEX_HEDG" and "DER_IRD_INTR"</control>
		<error_message>The gross value is not consistent with the sub-asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>123</id>
		<field_name>Long value of individual exposure</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;LongValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Long value amount for each Sub-asset type different from "DER_FEX_INVT", "DER_FEX_HEDG" and "DER_IRD_INTR" with long position value expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-086</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for sub-asset type equal to "DER_FEX_INVT", "DER_FEX_HEDG" and "DER_IRD_INTR"</control>
		<error_message>The long value is not consistent with the sub-asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>124</id>
		<field_name>Short value of individual exposure</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ShortValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Short value amount for each Sub-asset type different from "DER_FEX_INVT", "DER_FEX_HEDG" and "DER_IRD_INTR" with short position value expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-087</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for sub-asset type equal to "DER_FEX_INVT", "DER_FEX_HEDG" and "DER_IRD_INTR"</control>
		<error_message>The short value is not consistent with the sub-asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>127</id>
		<field_name>Notional value of turnover</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;NotionalValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The notional value of turnover in each relevant sub-asset type over the reporting months expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places. The notional amount should be reported only for derivatives sub-asset types (DER_EQD_EQD, DER_FID_FID, DER_CDS_CDS, DER_FEX_INV, DER_FEX_HED, DER_IRD_IRD, DER_CTY_CTY, DER_OTH_OTH). When no trades took place during the reporting period, '0'. should be reported for the sub-asset type code 'OTH_OTH_OTH'. </technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-088</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for sub-asset type different from DER_EQD_EQD,  DER_FID_FID, DER_CDS_CDS, DER_FEX_INV, DER_FEX_HED, DER_IRD_IRD, DER_CTY_CTY, DER_OTH_OTH</control>
		<error_message>The notional value is not consistent with the sub-asset type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>128</id>
		<field_name>Currency of the exposure</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ExposureCurrency&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>3-character currency code according to the ISO 4217  for each currency exposure</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-089</error_reference>
		<control>The currency code exists in the reference table of currencies</control>
		<error_message>The currency code is not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>129</id>
		<field_name>Currency Long Position Value</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;LongPositionValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Long position value amount for each currency exposure filled in without decimal places. The field is forbidden for currency of the exposure not filled in and optional otherwise</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-090</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for currency of the exposure not filled in and optional otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The long position value is not consistent with the currency of exposure.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>130</id>
		<field_name>Currency Short Position Value</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;ShortPositionValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Short position value amount for each currency exposure filled in without decimal places. The field is forbidden for currency of the exposure not filled in and optional otherwise</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-091</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for currency of the exposure not filled in and optional otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The short position value is not consistent with the currency of exposure.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>131</id>
		<field_name>Dominant influence company name</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityName&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Entity name. (no standard) It is strongly recommended to provide the full name corresponding to the allocated LEI code (or BIC code if any and LEI not available). The field is mandatory for AIF predominant type “Private Equity funds” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-092</error_reference>
		<control> The field is mandatory for AIF predominant type “Private Equity funds” and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The company name is not consistent with the AIF predominant type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>132</id>
		<field_name>Dominant influence company name</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityName&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Entity name. (no standard) It is strongly recommended to provide the full name corresponding to the allocated LEI code (or BIC code if any and LEI not available). The field is mandatory for AIF predominant type “Private Equity funds” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-093</error_reference>
		<control>Verify the correctness of the LEI code format rules following the calculation methodology of the 2-last check digits under validation rules using ISO 7064, Data Processing, Check Character Systems.</control>
		<error_message>The check digits of the LEI code are not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id></id>
		<field_name>Dominant influence company LEI code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationLEI&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>LEI code (ISO 17442 standard) or if not available the interim entity identifier: Characters 1-4: A four character prefix allocated uniquely to each LOU. •Characters 5-6: Two reserved characters set to zero. •Characters 7-18: Entity - specific part of the code generated and assigned by LOUs according to transparent, sound and robust allocation policies. •Characters 19-20: Two check digits The field is forbidden for AIF predominant type different from “Private Equity funds”.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-094</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for AIF predominant type different from “Private Equity funds”.</control>
		<error_message>The LEI code is not consistent with the AIF predominant type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>133</id>
		<field_name>Dominant influence company BIC code </field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationBIC&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>BIC code (ISO 9362 standard) The field is forbidden for AIF predominant type different from “Private Equity funds”.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-095</error_reference>
		<control> The field is forbidden for AIF predominant type different from “Private Equity funds”.</control>
		<error_message>The BIC code is not consistent with the AIF predominant type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>134</id>
		<field_name>Transaction type</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;TransactionType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The codes for the transaction type are:    - ACAP for "Acquisition capital"    - BOUT for "Buyouts"    - CONS for "Consolidations (industry roll-ups)"    - CDIV for "Corporate Divestitures"    - ESOP for "Employee Stock Ownership Plans"    - GCAP for "Growth Capital"    - RCAP for "Recapitalisation"    - SLIQ for "Shareholder Liquidity"    - TURN for "Turnarounds"    - OTHR for "Other transaction type" See Annex II - Table 5 (“Transaction type) The field is mandatory for AIF predominant type “Private Equity funds” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-096</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for AIF predominant type “Private Equity funds” and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The transaction type is not consistent with the AIF predominant type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>135</id>
		<field_name>Description of other transaction type</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;OtherTransactionTypeDescription&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Free text. The field is mandatory for transaction type equal to “OTHR” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-097</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for transaction type equal to “OTHR”</control>
		<error_message>The description for other transaction type is not consistent with the transaction type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>136</id>
		<field_name>% Voting rights</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;VotingRightsRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Rate expressed as a percentage. The field is mandatory for AIF predominant type “Private Equity funds” and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-098</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for AIF predominant type “Private Equity funds” and forbidden otherwise.</control>
		<error_message>The percentage of voting rights is not consistent with the AIF predominant type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>139</id>
		<field_name>Risk measure value</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RiskMeasureValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>This field is only authorised for risk measure type equal to "NET_EQTY_DELTA" and "NET_FX_DELTA" and "NET_CTY_DELTA" and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-099</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for  risk measure type different from "NET_DV01" and "NET_CS01" and mandatory otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The risk measure value is not consistent with the risk measure type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>140</id>
		<field_name>
			Risk measure value for bucket
		</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;LessFiveYearsRiskMeasureValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>This field is only authorised for risk measure type equal to "NET_DV01" and "NET_CS01" and forbidden otherwise</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-100</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for  risk measure type different from "NET_DV01" and "NET_CS01" and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The risk measure value is not consistent with the risk measure type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>141</id>
		<field_name>Risk measure value for bucket  5-15 years </field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;FifthteenYearsRiskMeasureValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>This field is only authorised for risk measure type equal to "NET_DV01" and "NET_CS01" and forbidden otherwise</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-101</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for  risk measure type different from "NET_DV01" and "NET_CS01" and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The risk measure value is not consistent with the risk measure type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>142</id>
		<field_name>Risk measure value for bucket  >15 years </field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;MoreFifthteenYearsRiskMeasureValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>This field is only authorised for risk measure type equal to "NET_DV01" and "NET_CS01" and forbidden otherwise</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-102</error_reference>
		<control>The field is mandatory for  risk measure type different from "NET_DV01" and "NET_CS01" and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The risk measure value is not consistent with the risk measure type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>143</id>
		<field_name>Risk measure value for Vega exposure at current market levels * </field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;CurrentMarketRiskMeasureValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>This field is only authorised for risk measure type equal to "VEGA_EXPO" and forbidden otherwise</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-103</error_reference>
		<control>This field is only authorised for risk measure type equal to "VEGA_EXPO" and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The risk measure value is not consistent with the risk measure type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>144</id>
		<field_name>Risk measure value for Vega exposure at market levels 10% lower *</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;LowerMarketRiskMeasureValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>This field is only authorised for risk measure type equal to "VEGA_EXPO" and forbidden otherwise</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-104</error_reference>
		<control>This field is only authorised for risk measure type equal to "VEGA_EXPO" and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The risk measure value is not consistent with the risk measure type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>145</id>
		<field_name>Risk measure value for Vega exposure at market levels10%  higher * </field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;HigherMarketRiskMeasureValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>This field is only authorised for risk measure type equal to "VEGA_EXPO" and forbidden otherwise</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-105</error_reference>
		<control>This field is only authorised for risk measure type equal to "VEGA_EXPO" and forbidden otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The risk measure value is not consistent with the risk measure type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>302</id>
		<field_name>VAR Value *</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;VARValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>This field is authorised only for risk measure type equal to "VAR" and forbidden otherwise. It is expressed as a percentage.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-106</error_reference>
		<control>This field is mandatory for risk measure type equal to "VAR" and forbidden otherwise. It is expressed as a percentage.</control>
		<error_message>The risk measure value is not consistent with the risk measure type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>146</id>
		<field_name>VAR Calculation Method Code Type *</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;VARCalculationMethodCodeType&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Allowed values are: - HISTO for Historical simulation - CARLO for Monte Carlo simulation - PARAM for Parametric This field is authorised only for risk measure type equal to "VAR" and forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-107</error_reference>
		<control>This field is mandatory for risk measure type equal to "VAR" and forbidden otherwise. </control>
		<error_message>The VAR calculation method is not consistent with the risk measure type.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>147</id>
		<field_name>Risk Measure description</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RiskMeasureDescription&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Free description. The field is mandatory for  risk measure values equal to 0 and optional otherwise. </technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-108</error_reference>
		<control>Mandatory for risk measure value equal to 0</control>
		<error_message>The Risk measure description is not consistent with the risk measure value.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>148</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of market value for securities traded on regulated exchanges</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RegulatedMarketRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Estimated % in terms of market value of securities traded on regulated exchange markets. Rate expressed as a percentage. The sum of the percentages reported by regulated exchanges and OTCs should be 100%  </technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-109</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the regulated exchange and OTC percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>149</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of market value for securities traded on OTC</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;OTCRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Estimated % in terms of market value of securities traded on OTC markets. Rate expressed as a percentage. The sum of the percentages reported by regulated exchanges and OTCs should be 100%  </technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-109</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the regulated exchange and OTC percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>150</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of trade volumes for derivatives traded on regulated exchanges</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RegulatedMarketRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Estimated % in terms of trade volumes of derivatives that are traded on regulated exchange markets. Rate expressed as a percentage. The sum of the percentages reported by regulated exchanges and OTCs should be 100%  </technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-111</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the regulated exchange and OTC percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>151</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of trade volumes for derivatives traded on OTC</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;OTCRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Estimated % in terms of trade volumes of derivatives that are traded on OTC markets. Rate expressed as a percentage. The sum of the percentages reported by regulated exchanges and OTCs should be 100%  </technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-111</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the regulated exchange and OTC percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>152</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of trade volumes for derivatives cleared by a CCP</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;CCPRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Estimated % in terms of trade volumes of derivatives transactions that are cleared by a CCP. Rate expressed as a percentage. The sum of the percentages reported for number of trade cleared by a CCP and bilaterraly should equal 100% .</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>WAF-001</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the CCP and bilaterally percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>153</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of trade volumes for derivatives cleared bilaterally</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;BilateralClearingRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Estimated % in terms of trade volumes of derivatives transactions that are cleared bilateraly. Rate expressed as a percentage. The sum of the percentages reported for number of trade cleared by a CCP and bilaterraly should equal 100% .</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>WAF-001</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the CCP and bilaterally percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>154</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of market value for repos trades cleared by a CCP</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;CCPRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Estimated % in terms of market value of repo trades that are cleared by a CCP. Rate expressed as a percentage. The sum of the percentages reported for the market value of repo trades cleared by a CCP, bilaterraly and on a tri-party basis should equal 100% .</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>WAF-002</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the CCP triparty and bilaterally percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>155</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of market value for repos trades cleared bilaterally</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;BilateralClearingRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Estimated % in terms of market value of repo trades that are cleared bilateraly. Rate expressed as a percentage. The sum of the percentages reported for the market value of repo trades cleared by a CCP, bilaterraly and on a tri-party basis should equal 100% .</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>WAF-002</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the CCP triparty and bilaterally percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>156</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of market value for repos trades cleared with triparty repos</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;TriPartyRepoClearingRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Estimated % in terms of market value of repo trades that are cleared via tri party repos. Rate expressed as a percentage. The sum of the percentages reported for the market value of repo trades cleared by a CCP, bilaterraly and on a tri-party basis should equal 100% .</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>WAF-002</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the CCP triparty and bilaterally percentages should be equal to 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>162</id>
		<field_name>Name of the counterparty to which the AIF has the greatest exposure</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityName&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Entity name. (no standard) It is strongly recommended to provide the full name corresponding to the allocated LEI code (or BIC code if any and LEI not available). Within each ranking, if the Counterparty exposure flag is equal to “true”, this field has to be reported. It is forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-113</error_reference>
		<control>Within each ranking, Mandatory for Counterparty exposure flag  (to which) equal to “true” Else Forbidden</control>
		<error_message>The counterparty name is not consistent with the counterparty exposure flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>163</id>
		<field_name>LEI code of the counterparty to which the AIF has the greatest exposure</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationLEI&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>LEI code (ISO 17442 standard) or if not available the interim entity identifier: Characters 1-4: A four character prefix allocated uniquely to each LOU. •Characters 5-6: Two reserved characters set to zero. •Characters 7-18: Entity - specific part of the code generated and assigned by LOUs according to transparent, sound and robust allocation policies. •Characters 19-20: Two check digits The field is forbidden for name of the counterparty not filled in and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-114</error_reference>
		<control>Verify the correctness of the LEI code format rules following the calculation methodology of the 2-last check digits under validation rules using ISO 7064, Data Processing, Check Character Systems.</control>
		<error_message>The check digits of the LEI code are not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>164</id>
		<field_name>LEI code of the counterparty to which the AIF has the greatest exposure</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationLEI&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>LEI code (ISO 17442 standard) or if not available the interim entity identifier: Characters 1-4: A four character prefix allocated uniquely to each LOU. •Characters 5-6: Two reserved characters set to zero. •Characters 7-18: Entity - specific part of the code generated and assigned by LOUs according to transparent, sound and robust allocation policies. •Characters 19-20: Two check digits The field is forbidden for name of the counterparty not filled in and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-115</error_reference>
		<control>Within each ranking, Forbidden for Counterparty exposure flag  (to which) equal to “false”</control>
		<error_message>The LEI code is not consistent with the counterparty exposure flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>164</id>
		<field_name>BIC code of the counterparty to which the AIF has the greatest exposure</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationBIC&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>BIC code (ISO 9362 standard). The field is forbidden for name of the counterparty not filled in and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-116</error_reference>
		<control>Within each ranking, Forbidden for Counterparty exposure flag  (to which) equal to “false”</control>
		<error_message>The BIC code is not consistent with the counterparty exposure flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>165</id>
		<field_name>NAV percentage of the total exposure value of the counterparties to which the AIF has the greatest exposure</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;CounterpartyTotalExposureRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Percentage of the NAV corresponding to the total exposure amount for each of the 5 greatest counterparty exposures to which the AIF has the greatest exposure. Within each ranking, if the Counterparty exposure flag is equal to “true”, this field has to be reported. It is forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-117</error_reference>
		<control>Within each ranking, Mandatory for Counterparty exposure flag  (to which) equal to “true” Else Forbidden</control>
		<error_message>The NAV percentage is not consistent with the counterparty exposure flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>166</id>
		<field_name>NAV percentage of the total exposure value of the counterparties to which the AIF has the greatest exposure</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;CounterpartyTotalExposureRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Percentage of the NAV corresponding to the total exposure amount for each of the 5 greatest counterparty exposures to which the AIF has the greatest exposure. Within each ranking, if the Counterparty exposure flag is equal to “true”, this field has to be reported. It is forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-118</error_reference>
		<control>The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on.</control>
		<error_message>The reported value is not consistent with the rank.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>168</id>
		<field_name>Name of the counterparty that has the greatest exposure to the AIF</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityName&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Entity name. (no standard) It is strongly recommended to provide the full name corresponding to the allocated LEI code (or BIC code if any and LEI not available). Within each ranking, if the Counterparty exposure flag is equal to “true”, this field has to be reported. It is forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-119</error_reference>
		<control>Within each ranking, Mandatory for Counterparty exposure flag  equal to “true” Else Forbidden</control>
		<error_message>The counterparty name is not consistent with the counterparty exposure flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>169</id>
		<field_name>LEI code of the counterparty that has the greatest exposure to the AIF</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationLEI&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>LEI code (ISO 17442 standard) or if not available the interim entity identifier: Characters 1-4: A four character prefix allocated uniquely to each LOU. •Characters 5-6: Two reserved characters set to zero. •Characters 7-18: Entity - specific part of the code generated and assigned by LOUs according to transparent, sound and robust allocation policies. •Characters 19-20: Two check digits The field is forbidden for name of the counterparty not filled in and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-120</error_reference>
		<control>Verify the correctness of the LEI code format rules following the calculation methodology of the 2-last check digits under validation rules using ISO 7064, Data Processing, Check Character Systems.</control>
		<error_message>The check digits of the LEI code are not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>170</id>
		<field_name>LEI code of the counterparty that has the greatest exposure to the AIF</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationLEI&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>LEI code (ISO 17442 standard) or if not available the interim entity identifier: Characters 1-4: A four character prefix allocated uniquely to each LOU. •Characters 5-6: Two reserved characters set to zero. •Characters 7-18: Entity - specific part of the code generated and assigned by LOUs according to transparent, sound and robust allocation policies. •Characters 19-20: Two check digits The field is forbidden for name of the counterparty not filled in and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-121</error_reference>
		<control>Within each ranking, Forbidden for Counterparty exposure flag  (to which) equal to “false”</control>
		<error_message>The LEI code is not consistent with the counterparty exposure flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>170</id>
		<field_name>BIC code of the counterparty that has the greatest exposure to the AIF</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationBIC&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>BIC code (ISO 9362 standard) The field is forbidden for name of the counterparty not filled in and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-122</error_reference>
		<control>Within each ranking, Forbidden for Counterparty exposure flag  (to which) equal to “false”</control>
		<error_message>The BIC code is not consistent with the counterparty exposure flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>171</id>
		<field_name>NAV percentage of the total exposure value of the counterparties that have the greatest exposure to the AIF</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;CounterpartyTotalExposureRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Percentage of the NAV corresponding to the total exposure amount for each of the 5 greatest counterparty exposures that has the greatest to the AIF. Within each ranking, if the Counterparty exposure flag is equal to “true”, this field has to be reported. It is forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-123</error_reference>
		<control>Within each ranking, Mandatory for Counterparty exposure flag  equal to “true” Else Forbidden</control>
		<error_message>The NAV percentage is not consistent with the counterparty exposure flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>172</id>
		<field_name>NAV percentage of the total exposure value of the counterparties that have the greatest exposure to the AIF</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;CounterpartyTotalExposureRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Percentage of the NAV corresponding to the total exposure amount for each of the 5 greatest counterparty exposures that has the greatest to the AIF. Within each ranking, if the Counterparty exposure flag is equal to “true”, this field has to be reported. It is forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-124</error_reference>
		<control>The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on.</control>
		<error_message>The reported value is not consistent with the rank.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>173</id>
		<field_name>Ranking (CCP)</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;Ranking&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The ranking admitted are: - 1 for “first CCP exposure”; - 2 for “second CCP exposure”; and - 3 for “third top CCP exposure”.  If the Direct clearing flag is equal to “true”, at least rank “1” has to be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-125</error_reference>
		<control>If the Direct clearing flag equal to “true”, at least rank “1” has to be reported.   </control>
		<error_message></error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>175</id>
		<field_name>LEI code of CCP with greatest exposure</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationLEI&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>LEI code (ISO 17442 standard) or if not available the interim entity identifier: Characters 1-4: A four character prefix allocated uniquely to each LOU. •Characters 5-6: Two reserved characters set to zero. •Characters 7-18: Entity - specific part of the code generated and assigned by LOUs according to transparent, sound and robust allocation policies. •Characters 19-20: Two check digits The field is forbidden for Direct clearing flag equal to "false" and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-126</error_reference>
		<control>Verify the correctness of the LEI code format rules following the calculation methodology of the 2-last check digits under validation rules using ISO 7064, Data Processing, Check Character Systems.</control>
		<error_message>The LEI code is not consistent with the counterparty exposure flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>178</id>
		<field_name>Exposure value of CCP with greatest exposure</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;CCPExposureValue&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Exposure amount for each 3 greatest CCP exposures expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places. The field is mandatory for Direct clearing flag equal to "true" for rank "1" and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-127</error_reference>
		<control>The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on.</control>
		<error_message>The reported value is not consistent with the rank.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>178</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of portfolio liquidity in 0 to 1 day</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;PortfolioLiquidityInDays0to1Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The percentage of portfolio capable of being liquidated within 1 day or less. The total sum of the percentage of the fund's portfolio that is capable of being liquidated within each of the liquidity periods specified should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-128</error_reference>
		<control>The total sum of the percentage of the fund's portfolio that is capable of being liquidated should equal 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>179</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of portfolio liquidity in 2 to 7 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;PortfolioLiquidityInDays2to7Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The percentage of portfolio capable of being liquidated in 2 to 7 days. The total sum of the percentage of the fund's portfolio that is capable of being liquidated within each of the liquidity periods specified should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-128</error_reference>
		<control>The total sum of the percentage of the fund's portfolio that is capable of being liquidated should equal 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>180</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of portfolio liquidity in 8 to 30 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;PortfolioLiquidityInDays8to30Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The percentage of portfolio capable of being liquidated in 8 to 30 days. The total sum of the percentage of the fund's portfolio that is capable of being liquidated within each of the liquidity periods specified should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-128</error_reference>
		<control>The total sum of the percentage of the fund's portfolio that is capable of being liquidated should equal 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>181</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of portfolio liquidity in 31 to 90 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;PortfolioLiquidityInDays31to90Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The percentage of portfolio capable of being liquidated in 31 to 90 days. The total sum of the percentage of the fund's portfolio that is capable of being liquidated within each of the liquidity periods specified should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-128</error_reference>
		<control>The total sum of the percentage of the fund's portfolio that is capable of being liquidated should equal 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>182</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of portfolio liquidity in 91 to 180 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;PortfolioLiquidityInDays91to180Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The percentage of portfolio capable of being liquidated in 91 to 180 days. The total sum of the percentage of the fund's portfolio that is capable of being liquidated within each of the liquidity periods specified should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-128</error_reference>
		<control>The total sum of the percentage of the fund's portfolio that is capable of being liquidated should equal 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>183</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of portfolio liquidity in 181 to 365 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;PortfolioLiquidityInDays181to365Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The percentage of portfolio capable of being liquidated in 181 to 365 days. The total sum of the percentage of the fund's portfolio that is capable of being liquidated within each of the liquidity periods specified should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-128</error_reference>
		<control>The total sum of the percentage of the fund's portfolio that is capable of being liquidated should equal 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>184</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of portfolio liquidity in more than 365 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;PortfolioLiquidityInDays365MoreRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The percentage of portfolio capable of being liquidated in more than 365 days. The total sum of the percentage of the fund's portfolio that is capable of being liquidated within each of the liquidity periods specified should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-128</error_reference>
		<control>The total sum of the percentage of the fund's portfolio that is capable of being liquidated should equal 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>186</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of investor liquidity in 0 to 1 day</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;InvestorLiquidityInDays0to1Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Breakdown of the NAV divided among the 1 day or less period depending on  the shortest period within which the invested funds could be withdrawn or investors could receive redemption payments. The total should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-129</error_reference>
		<control>The total of the breakdown should equal 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>187</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of investor liquidity in 2 to 7 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;InvestorLiquidityInDays2to7Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Breakdown of the NAV divided among the “2 to 7 days” period depending on  the shortest period within which the invested funds could be withdrawn or investors could receive redemption payments. The total should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-129</error_reference>
		<control>The total of the breakdown should equal 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>188</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of investor liquidity in 8 to 30 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;InvestorLiquidityInDays8to30Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Breakdown of the NAV divided among the “8 to 30 days” period depending on  the shortest period within which the invested funds could be withdrawn or investors could receive redemption payments. The total should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-129</error_reference>
		<control>The total of the breakdown should equal 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>189</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of investor liquidity in 31 to 90 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;InvestorLiquidityInDays31to90Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Breakdown of the NAV divided among the “31 to 90 days” period depending on  the shortest period within which the invested funds could be withdrawn or investors could receive redemption payments. The total should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-129</error_reference>
		<control>The total of the breakdown should equal 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>190</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of investor liquidity in 91 to 180 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;InvestorLiquidityInDays91to180Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Breakdown of the NAV divided among the “91 to 180 days” period depending on  the shortest period within which the invested funds could be withdrawn or investors could receive redemption payments. The total should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-129</error_reference>
		<control>The total of the breakdown should equal 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>191</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of investor liquidity in 181 to 365 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;InvestorLiquidityInDays181to365Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Breakdown of the NAV divided among the “181 to 365 days” period depending on  the shortest period within which the invested funds could be withdrawn or investors could receive redemption payments. The total should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-129</error_reference>
		<control>The total of the breakdown should equal 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>192</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of investor liquidity in more than 365 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;InvestorLiquidityInDays365MoreRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Breakdown of the NAV divided among the “more than 365 days” period depending on  the shortest period within which the invested funds could be withdrawn or investors could receive redemption payments. The total should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-129</error_reference>
		<control>The total of the breakdown should equal 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>194</id>
		<field_name>Investor Redemption Frequency</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;InvestorRedemptionFrequency&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The frequency of investor redemptions. If there are multiple classes of shares or units, the frequency reported is for the largest share class by NAV. The alloxed values are:    - D for “Daily”    - W for “Weekly”    - F for “Fortnightly”    - M for “Monthly”    - Q for “Quarterly”    - H for “Half-yearly”    - Y for “Yearly”    - O for “Other”    - N for “None” see Annex II - Table 6 The field is forbidden for Withdrawal redemption rights flag equal to "false" and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-130</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for Withdrawal redemption rights flag false and optional otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The investor redemption frequency is not consistent with the withdrawal redemption rights flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>195</id>
		<field_name>Investor Redemption Notice Period</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;InvestorRedemptionNoticePeriod&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The notice period required by investors for redemptions in days. If there are multiple classes of shares or units, the notice period reported is the asset weighted notice period. The number of days is expressed without decimal places when weighted. The field is forbidden for Withdrawal redemption rights flag equal to "false" and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-131</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for Withdrawal redemption rights flag false and optional otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The investor redemption notice period is not consistent with the withdrawal redemption rights flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>196</id>
		<field_name>Investor Redemption Lock Up Period</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;InvestorRedemptionLockUpPeriod&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>The investor lock-up period in days. If there are multiple classes of shares or units, the notice period reported is the asset weighted notice period. The number of days expressed without decimal places when weighted. The field is forbidden for Withdrawal redemption rights flag equal to "false" and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-132</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for Withdrawal redemption rights flag false and optional otherwise</control>
		<error_message>The investor redemption lock-up is not consistent with the withdrawal redemption rights flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>211</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of financing amount in 0 to 1 day</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;TotalFinancingInDays0to1Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Breakdown of the total financing amount divided among the 1 day or less period depending on  the longest period for which the creditor is contractually committed to provide such financing. The total should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-133</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the percentages of financing amount should be 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>212</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of financing amount in 2 to 7 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;TotalFinancingInDays2to7Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Breakdown of the total financing amount divided among the “2 to 7 days” period depending on  the longest period for which the creditor is contractually committed to provide such financing. The total should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-133</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the percentages of financing amount should be 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>213</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of financing amount in 8 to 30 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;TotalFinancingInDays8to30Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Breakdown of the total financing amount divided among the “8 to 30 days” period depending on  the longest period for which the creditor is contractually committed to provide such financing. The total should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-133</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the percentages of financing amount should be 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>214</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of financing amount in 31 to 90 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;TotalFinancingInDays31to90Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Breakdown of the total financing amount divided among the “91 to 180 days” period depending on  the longest period for which the creditor is contractually committed to provide such financing. The total should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-133</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the percentages of financing amount should be 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>215</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of financing amount in 91 to 180 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;TotalFinancingInDays91to180Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Breakdown of the total financing amount divided among the “8 to 30 days” period depending on  the longest period for which the creditor is contractually committed to provide such financing. The total should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-133</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the percentages of financing amount should be 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>216</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of financing amount in 181 to 365 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;TotalFinancingInDays181to365Rate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Breakdown of the total financing amount divided among the “181 to 365 days” period depending on  the longest period for which the creditor is contractually committed to provide such financing. The total should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-133</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the percentages of financing amount should be 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>217</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of financing amount longer than 365 days</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;TotalFinancingInDays365MoreRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Breakdown of the total financing amount divided among the “more than 365 days” period depending on  the longest period for which the creditor is contractually committed to provide such financing. The total should equal 100%.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-133</error_reference>
		<control>The sum of the percentages of financing amount should be 100%. </control>
		<error_message>The sum of the percentages should be equal to 100%.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>219</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of gross investment returns for January</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateJanuary&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Gross investment returns or IRR of the AIF for January (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the January rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-134</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the January rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>220</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of gross investment returns for February</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateFebruary&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Gross investment returns or IRR of the AIF for February (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the February rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-134</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the February rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>221</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of gross investment returns for March</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateMarch&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>0</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-134</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the March rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>222</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of gross investment returns for April</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateApril&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Gross investment returns or IRR of the AIF for April (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the April rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-134</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the April rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>223</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of gross investment returns for May</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateMay&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Gross investment returns or IRR of the AIF for May (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the May rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-134</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the May rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>224</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of gross investment returns for June</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateJune&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Gross investment returns or IRR of the AIF for June (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the June rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-134</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the June rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>225</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of gross investment returns for July</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateJuly&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Gross investment returns or IRR of the AIF for July (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the July rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-134</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the July rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>226</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of gross investment returns for August</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateAugust&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Gross investment returns or IRR of the AIF for August (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the August rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-134</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the August rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>227</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of gross investment returns for September</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateSeptember&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Gross investment returns or IRR of the AIF for September (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the September rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-134</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the September rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>228</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of gross investment returns for October</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateOctober&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Gross investment returns or IRR of the AIF for October (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the October rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-134</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the October rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>229</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of gross investment returns for November</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateNovember&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Gross investment returns or IRR of the AIF for November (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the November rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-134</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the November rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>230</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of gross investment returns for December</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateDecember&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Gross investment returns or IRR of the AIF for December (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the December rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-134</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the December rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>231</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of net investment returns for January</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateJanuary&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Net investment returns or IRR of the AIF for January (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the January rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-135</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the January rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>232</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of net investment returns for February</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateFebruary&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Net investment returns or IRR of the AIF for February (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the February rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-135</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the February rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>233</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of net investment returns for March</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateMarch&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Net investment returns or IRR of the AIF for March (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the March rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-135</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the March rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>234</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of net investment returns for April</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateApril&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Net investment returns or IRR of the AIF for April (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the April rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-135</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the April rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>235</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of net investment returns for May</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateMay&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Net investment returns or IRR of the AIF for May (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the May rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-135</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the May rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>236</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of net investment returns for June</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateJune&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Net investment returns or IRR of the AIF for June (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the June rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-135</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the June rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>237</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of net investment returns for July</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateJuly&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Net investment returns or IRR of the AIF for July (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the July rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-135</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the July rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>238</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of net investment returns for August</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateAugust&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Net investment returns or IRR of the AIF for August (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the August rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-135</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the August rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>239</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of net investment returns for September</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateSeptember&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Net investment returns or IRR of the AIF for September (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the September rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-135</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the September rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>240</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of net investment returns for October</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateOctober&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Net investment returns or IRR of the AIF for October (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the October rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-135</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the October rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>241</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of net investment returns for November</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateNovember&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Net investment returns or IRR of the AIF for November (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the November rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-135</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the November rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>242</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of net investment returns for December</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateDecember&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Net investment returns or IRR of the AIF for December (in %, gross of management and performance fees). Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the December rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-135</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the December rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>243</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of NAV change for January</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateJanuary&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>December to January changes in NAV including the impact of subscriptions and redemptions Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the January rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-136</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the January rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>244</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of NAV change for February</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateFebruary&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>January to February changes in NAV including the impact of subscriptions and redemptions Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the February rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-136</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the February rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>245</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of NAV change for March</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateMarch&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>February to March changes in NAV including the impact of subscriptions and redemptions Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the March rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-136</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the March rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>246</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of NAV change for April</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateApril&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>March to April changes in NAV including the impact of subscriptions and redemptions Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the April rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-136</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the April rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>247</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of NAV change for May</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateMay&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>April to May changes in NAV including the impact of subscriptions and redemptions Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the May rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-136</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the May rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>248</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of NAV change for June</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateJune&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>May to June changes in NAV including the impact of subscriptions and redemptions Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the June rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-136</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the June rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>249</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of NAV change for July</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateJuly&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>June to July changes in NAV including the impact of subscriptions and redemptions Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the July rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-136</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the July rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>250</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of NAV change for August</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateAugust&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>July to August changes in NAV including the impact of subscriptions and redemptions Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the August rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-136</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the August rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>251</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of NAV change for September</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateSeptember&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>August to September changes in NAV including the impact of subscriptions and redemptions Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the September rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-136</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the September rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>252</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of NAV change for October</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateOctober&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>September to October changes in NAV including the impact of subscriptions and redemptions Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the October rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-136</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the October rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>253</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of NAV change for November</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateNovember&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>October to November changes in NAV including the impact of subscriptions and redemptions Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the November rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-136</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the November rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>254</id>
		<field_name>Percentage of NAV change for December</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;RateDecember&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>November to December changes in NAV including the impact of subscriptions and redemptions Rate expressed as a percentage. For each calendar year, the December rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-136</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the December rate should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March rates may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June rates may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September rates may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December rates may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June rates may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month rates may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month rate is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>255</id>
		<field_name>Number of subscriptions for January</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityJanuary&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of subscriptions during January.  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the January quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-137</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the January quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>256</id>
		<field_name>Number of subscriptions for February</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityFebruary&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of subscriptions during February  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the February quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-137</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the February quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>257</id>
		<field_name>Number of subscriptions for March</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityMarch&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of subscriptions during March  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the March quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-137</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the March quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>258</id>
		<field_name>Number of subscriptions for April</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityApril&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of subscriptions during April  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the April quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-137</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the April quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>259</id>
		<field_name>Number of subscriptions for May</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityMay&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of subscriptions during May  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the May quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-137</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the May quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>260</id>
		<field_name>Number of subscriptions for June</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityJune&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of subscriptions during June  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the June quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-137</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the June quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>261</id>
		<field_name>Number of subscriptions for July</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityJuly&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of subscriptions during July  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the July quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-137</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the July quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>262</id>
		<field_name>Number of subscriptions for August</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityAugust&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of subscriptions during August  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the August quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-137</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the August quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>263</id>
		<field_name>Number of subscriptions for September</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantitySeptember&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of subscriptions during September  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the September quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-137</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the September quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>264</id>
		<field_name>Number of subscriptions for October</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityOctober&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of subscriptions during October  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the October quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-137</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the October quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>265</id>
		<field_name>Number of subscriptions for November</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityNovember&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of subscriptions during November  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the November quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-137</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the November quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>266</id>
		<field_name>Number of subscriptions for December</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityDecember&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of subscriptions during December  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the December quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-137</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the December quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>267</id>
		<field_name>Number of redemptions for January</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityJanuary&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of redemptions during January.  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the January quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-138</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the January quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>268</id>
		<field_name>Number of redemptions for February</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityFebruary&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of redemptions during February  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the February quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-138</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the February quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>269</id>
		<field_name>Number of redemptions for March</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityMarch&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of redemptions during March  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the March quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-138</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the March quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>270</id>
		<field_name>Number of redemptions for April</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityApril&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of redemptions during April  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the April quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-138</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the April quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>271</id>
		<field_name>Number of redemptions for May</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityMay&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of redemptions during May  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the May quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-138</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the May quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>272</id>
		<field_name>Number of redemptions for June</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityJune&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of redemptions during June  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the June quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-138</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the June quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>273</id>
		<field_name>Number of redemptions for July</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityJuly&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of redemptions during July  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the July quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-138</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the July quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>274</id>
		<field_name>Number of redemptions for August</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityAugust&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of redemptions during August  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the August quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-138</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the August quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>275</id>
		<field_name>Number of redemptions for September</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantitySeptember&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of redemptions during September  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the September quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-138</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the September quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>276</id>
		<field_name>Number of redemptions for October</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityOctober&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of redemptions during October  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the October quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-138</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the October quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>277</id>
		<field_name>Number of redemptions for November</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityNovember&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of redemptions during November  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the November quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-138</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the November quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>278</id>
		<field_name>Number of redemptions for December</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;QuantityDecember&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Number of redemptions during December  Number filled in without decimal places. For each calendar year, the December quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-138</error_reference>
		<control>For each calendar year, the December quantity should be reported only once. For Q1 reporting period, only January, February and March quantities may be reported. For Q2 reporting period, only April, May and June quantities may be reported. For Q3 reporting period, only July, August and September quantities may be reported. For Q4 reporting period, only October, November and December quantities may be reported. For H1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May and June quantities may be reported. For H2 reporting period, only July, August, September, October, November and December quantities may be reported. For Y1 reporting period, all month quantities may be reported. For X1 reporting period, only January, February, March, April, May, June, July, August and September rates may be reported. For X2 reporting period, only April, May, June, July, August, September, October, November and December rates may be reported.</control>
		<error_message>The month quantity is not consistent with the reporting period.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>282</id>
		<field_name>Rehypothecated percentage of collateral amount posted to all counterparties</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;AllCounterpartyCollateralRehypothecatedRate&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Percentage of the amounts of collateral and other credit support (that the AIF has posted to counterparties) that have been rehypothecated by counterparties. Rate expressed as a percentage.  The field is forbidden for Rehypothecation flag equal to "false" and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-139</error_reference>
		<control>The field is forbidden for rehypothecation flag false and optional otherwise.</control>
		<error_message></error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>291</id>
		<field_name>Controlled structure LEI code</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationLEI&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>LEI code (ISO 17442 standard) or if not available the interim entity identifier: Characters 1-4: A four character prefix allocated uniquely to each LOU. •Characters 5-6: Two reserved characters set to zero. •Characters 7-18: Entity - specific part of the code generated and assigned by LOUs according to transparent, sound and robust allocation policies. •Characters 19-20: Two check digits</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-140</error_reference>
		<control>Verify the correctness of the LEI code format rules following the calculation methodology of the 2-last check digits under validation rules using ISO 7064, Data Processing, Check Character Systems.</control>
		<error_message>The check digits of the LEI code are not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>298</id>
		<field_name>Name of the largest source of borrowed cash or securities</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityName&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Entity name. (no standard) It is strongly recommended to provide the full name corresponding to the allocated LEI code (or BIC code if any and LEI not available). Within each ranking, if the Borrowing source flag is equal to “true”, this field has to be reported. It is forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-141</error_reference>
		<control>Within each ranking, Mandatory for Borrowing source flag equal to “true” Else Forbidden</control>
		<error_message></error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>299</id>
		<field_name>LEI code of the largest source of borrowed cash or securities</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationLEI&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>LEI code (ISO 17442 standard) or if not available the interim entity identifier: Characters 1-4: A four character prefix allocated uniquely to each LOU. •Characters 5-6: Two reserved characters set to zero. •Characters 7-18: Entity - specific part of the code generated and assigned by LOUs according to transparent, sound and robust allocation policies. •Characters 19-20: Two check digits The field is forbidden for name of the counterparty not filled in and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-142</error_reference>
		<control>Verify the correctness of the LEI code format rules following the calculation methodology of the 2-last check digits under validation rules using ISO 7064, Data Processing, Check Character Systems.</control>
		<error_message>The check digits of the LEI code are not correct.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>300</id>
		<field_name>LEI code of the largest source of borrowed cash or securities</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationLEI&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>LEI code (ISO 17442 standard) or if not available the interim entity identifier: Characters 1-4: A four character prefix allocated uniquely to each LOU. •Characters 5-6: Two reserved characters set to zero. •Characters 7-18: Entity - specific part of the code generated and assigned by LOUs according to transparent, sound and robust allocation policies. •Characters 19-20: Two check digits The field is forbidden for name of the counterparty not filled in and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-143</error_reference>
		<control>Within each ranking, Forbidden  for Borrowing source flag equal to “false” </control>
		<error_message>The LEI code is not consistent with the borrowing source flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>300</id>
		<field_name>BIC code of the largest source of borrowed cash or securities</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;EntityIdentificationBIC&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>BIC code (ISO 9362 standard) The field is forbidden for name of the counterparty not filled in and optional otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-144</error_reference>
		<control>Within each ranking, Forbidden  for Borrowing source flag equal to “false” </control>
		<error_message>The BIC code is not consistent with the borrowing source flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>301</id>
		<field_name>Received leverage amount</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;LeverageAmount&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Leverage amount received from each of the 5 largest sources of borrowed cash or securities expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places. Within each ranking, if the Borrowing source flag is equal to “true”, this field has to be reported. It is forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-145</error_reference>
		<control>Within each ranking, Mandatory for Borrowing source flag equal to “true” Else Forbidden</control>
		<error_message>The leverage amount is not consistent with the borrowing source flag.</error_message>
	</rule>
	<rule>
		<id>302</id>
		<field_name>Received leverage amount</field_name>
		<element_name>&lt;LeverageAmount&gt;</element_name>
		<technical_guidance>Leverage amount received from each of the 5 largest sources of borrowed cash or securities expressed in base currency filled in without decimal places. Within each ranking, if the Borrowing source flag is equal to “true”, this field has to be reported. It is forbidden otherwise.</technical_guidance>
		<error_reference>CAF-146</error_reference>
		<control>The ranks that are assigned to the reported values should be consistent in relation to each other. First rank values are above or equal to the second rank values and so on.</control>
		<error_message>The reported value is not consistent with the rank.</error_message>
	</rule>
</rules>