<errors>
	<error>
		<code>FIL-009</code>
		<message>The authority key file attribute is not consistent with the sending</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>FIL-015</code>
		<message>The authority key file attribute is invalid and should an EU or EEA country</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-001</code>
		<message>The AIF record with "INIT" filing type has been already provided and will not be recorded twice.</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-002</code>
		<message>The reporting period start date is not allowed.</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-003</code>
		<message>The reporting period end date is not allowed</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-004</code>
		<message>The quarter for the AIMF reporting obligation change should be reported</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-005</code>
		<message>The jurisdiction of the AIF is not correct.</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-006</code>
		<message>The AIFM national code does not exist in the ESMA Register.</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-007</code>
		<message>Verify the correctness of the LEI code format rules following the calculation methodology of the 2-last check digits</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-008</code>
		<message>The country code exists in the reference table of countries</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-009</code>
		<message>The field is mandatory when the  old AIFM national identifier - Reporting Member State is filled in.</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-010</code>
		<message>The MIC code is not correct</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-011</code>
		<message>The field is mandatory for market code type different from  “NOT”.</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-012</code>
		<message>The reported value is not consistent with the rank.</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-013</code>
		<message>The aggregated value is not consistent with the sub-asset type.</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-014</code>
		<message>The reported value is not consistent with the rank.</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-016</code>
		<message>The total AuM amount in base currency is not consistent with the  total AuM amount in Euro.</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-017</code>
		<message>The currency code does not exist in the reference table of currencies</message>
	</error>
	<error>
		<code>CAM-020</code>
		<message>The reference rate description is not consistent with the reference rate type.</message>
	</error>
</errors>